<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Loans101</title>
    <link>http://loans101.com.au/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Loans101</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Loans101</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 21:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://loans101.com.au/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Borrowing Power Calculator</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/borrowing_power_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/borrowing_power_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If my wife is working as casual from last 10 months then how much % of her income is countable towards landing mortgage? and how long does it takes to get the preapproved home loan?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/if-my-wife-is-working-as-casual-from-last-10-months-then-how-much-of-her-income-is-countable-towards-landing-mortgage-and-how-long-does-it-takes-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/if-my-wife-is-working-as-casual-from-last-10-months-then-how-much-of-her-income-is-countable-towards-landing-mortgage-and-how-long-does-it-takes-to/</guid>
      <description>There are numerous lenders who will accept 100% of your wife income, including ANZ. Turn around times for a pre-approval (depending on the lender) are anywhere from 24-72 hours. Feel free to contact me via my profile if you&amp;rsquo;d like more info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just wondering as it comes up with.... No deals with bad credit. Do you not help people with bad credit, to get a home loan?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/just-wondering-as-it-comes-up-with-no-deals-with-bad-credit-do-you-not-help-people-with-bad-credit-to-get-a-home-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/just-wondering-as-it-comes-up-with-no-deals-with-bad-credit-do-you-not-help-people-with-bad-credit-to-get-a-home-loan/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to help people with bad credit. There are definitely lenders in the non conforming space who specialise in this area. The loan product and interest rates will depend on the type of &amp;ldquo;bad credit&amp;rdquo;, such as missed repayments, defaults or a high number credit enquiries. Based on this, we can match the most appropriate lender to your situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can i get a home loan with a low repayments and probably 5% down payment only?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/can-i-get-a-home-loan-with-a-low-repayments-and-probably-5-down-payment-only/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/can-i-get-a-home-loan-with-a-low-repayments-and-probably-5-down-payment-only/</guid>
      <description>You most definitely can obtain a home loan with 5% deposit, provided that you can also service the loan. Ensure you have sufficient funds for stamp duty, and related fees. If you would like some guidance around this, please click on my profile and contact me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am interested in seeking the best competitive investment loan for my situation which is I have 3 investment properties and total outstanding is about $500K . Currently, I am on P&amp;I payments with one of the major banks. I am also keen to see if there are competitive interest only loans for my situation.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-interested-in-seeking-the-best-competitive-investment-loan-for-my-situation-which-is-i-have-3-investment-properties-and-total-outstanding-is-abou/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-interested-in-seeking-the-best-competitive-investment-loan-for-my-situation-which-is-i-have-3-investment-properties-and-total-outstanding-is-abou/</guid>
      <description>Special investment rates for P&amp;amp;I, must be under 80% LVR: 3.74% for 2 year fixed 3.79% for 3 year fixed and variable starting from 3.99% Naturally, properties need to be acceptable security and serviceability needs to be met.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking to buy another home but the banks are very tight on equity.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/looking-to-buy-another-home-but-the-banks-are-very-tight-on-equity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/looking-to-buy-another-home-but-the-banks-are-very-tight-on-equity/</guid>
      <description>It is difficult at the moment with unsure values of properties and different banks treating the same property very differently. As a broker that is what we trained to do, take the running around off you and make the process more user friendly. To assist you, I would need to know some more detailed information. My contact details are in my profile, and i would be happy to assist you in working through the information to see if we can find you a solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My partner &amp; I have 7 properties, 1 being principal address and 6 investments. The properties in total are worth around $2.4million with a mortgage of $570k , which is split over 2 investment properties. I am 46 and partner is 69 . I live off my investments as I am retired and my partner works part time earning around $26k a year. The rental income is $2085pw repayment is $1969 for one investment and the other $1083 for the other. I have $226k in super and partner around $12k. My exit strategy is when I am 68 and would like to continue to invest. In my own name I would like to borrow for 1 investment and would like to know how much I can borrow and if possible to borrow.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/my-partner-i-have-7-properties-1-being-principal-address-and-6-investments-the-properties-in-total-are-worth-around-24million-with-a-mortgage-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/my-partner-i-have-7-properties-1-being-principal-address-and-6-investments-the-properties-in-total-are-worth-around-24million-with-a-mortgage-of/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your enquiry, and also the extra information you have provided. A number of factors would need to be discussed to aid you in your investment enquiries, to ensure that you not only are able to proceed with your investment strategy, but also that we are able to structure the acquisition to provide you ongoing protection for you and your assets. I am sure that I can help you in regards to your future investment strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suncorp Bank to Basic Loan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/suncorp-bank-to-basic-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 12:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/suncorp-bank-to-basic-loan/</guid>
      <description>1. Features  [ ] Offset Account
 [x] Redraw Facility
 [x] Allow Extra Repayment
 [x] Allow Loan Increase
 [x] Split Loans
  2. Upfront Fees This is a fee that may be payable by the borrower to a lender prior to or at the application stage, of the lending process. An example of an upfront fee maybe an Application fee (while some may charge upfront, most do not), or Valuation fee (some lenders may charge, while others will cover this cost)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loan Repayment Calculator</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/loan_repayment_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/loan_repayment_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are currently looking to refinance our home loan We hace 2 loans with bankwest one for our land and one for our house. The house is on the land. The value of our house is 650000 we currently owe 390000 aprox. We are looking for a loan of 415000 because we want to do aditions to the property. We are looking for a 5 yr fixed interest loan with a offset account . And no ongoing fees over 25 yrs.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/we-are-currently-looking-to-refinance-our-home-loan-we-hace-2-loans-with-bankwest-one-for-our-land-and-one-for-our-house-the-house-is-on-the-land-th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/we-are-currently-looking-to-refinance-our-home-loan-we-hace-2-loans-with-bankwest-one-for-our-land-and-one-for-our-house-the-house-is-on-the-land-th/</guid>
      <description>Based on the information you have provided there are a number of options that suit the criteria you have listed above. For a 5 year fixed rate with an offset account you could be looking at interest rates of about 4.19% right through to 4.79%. Some of these banks offer 100% offset accounts on their fixed rate loans and some will offer a shaded offset account, say around 50% to 70% offset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We were in the middle of saving for a deposit and a block of land has become available. we have $24000 in savings and a further $25000 as a gift. the property is $495000. if we want to put a deposit down on the block can we access this from the loan ? we are also very anxious how long is the process of approval before we would be able to make an offer?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/we-were-in-the-middle-of-saving-for-a-deposit-and-a-block-of-land-has-become-available-we-have-24000-in-savings-and-a-further-25000-as-a-gift-the/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/we-were-in-the-middle-of-saving-for-a-deposit-and-a-block-of-land-has-become-available-we-have-24000-in-savings-and-a-further-25000-as-a-gift-the/</guid>
      <description>Great Question - You have the 5% genuine savings for the land and Im wondering if the gift has been in your account for &amp;gt; 3 months - if so then this might make up the balance of the house and land 5% needed. If you are looking to build asap - the rent or board you are currently paying is not included in servicing if both loans are put in at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just wondering if you can get a loan for someone on 820 visa?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/just-wondering-if-you-can-get-a-loan-for-someone-on-820-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/just-wondering-if-you-can-get-a-loan-for-someone-on-820-visa/</guid>
      <description>You can providing your partner has Australian Citizenship and you have proof of your relationship. Loan will be restricted to 80% of property purchase. Let me know if I can help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for an investment property loan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/looking-for-an-investment-property-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/looking-for-an-investment-property-loan/</guid>
      <description>Happy to assist. There are many variables at the moment when it comes to investment lending e.g. interest only versus principal + interest, how much deposit you have . Just a couple of things that will impact the interest rate as all lenders have different requirements. Contact me through my profile and we can chat then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We have an existing loan would like to refinance to incorporate credit card debt. We are both retired and on pension. Our exsisting variable rate is over 30years. Would there be another lender /better rates than we have now. $75,0000 @ 4.45%. </title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/we-have-an-existing-loan-would-like-to-refinance-to-incorporate-credit-card-debt-we-are-both-retired-and-on-pension-our-exsisting-variable-rate-is-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/we-have-an-existing-loan-would-like-to-refinance-to-incorporate-credit-card-debt-we-are-both-retired-and-on-pension-our-exsisting-variable-rate-is-o/</guid>
      <description>Depending on your pensions - there are rates from 3.67% for refinance with cash out for debt consolidation. Would love to help you. Please contact me via my Profile Page. I look forward to hearing from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am looking at buying a block of land and subdividing into 2. Cost of subdivision will be about $10,000. Land will be $95-100k. The land will be worth about $80k per block once divided. I am looking at building 2 house ( 1 on each block ) which will cone in around $200k per house. Once complet the houses will be worth about $360k each. Interested in a loan that gives me maximum leverage as I have another house I am going to start in before this. I owe about $97000k on the land which is valued by ANZ at $160k. The house build will be $330k whilst an agent has valued the finished home at $580k-$630k</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-looking-at-buying-a-block-of-land-and-subdividing-into-2-cost-of-subdivision-will-be-about-10000-land-will-be-95100k-the-land-will-be-wort/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-looking-at-buying-a-block-of-land-and-subdividing-into-2-cost-of-subdivision-will-be-about-10000-land-will-be-95100k-the-land-will-be-wort/</guid>
      <description>We can certainly assist in this type of project. Of course, the amount you can borrow will depend on your current financial position and the structure of ownership of these properties. You may also need to consider the taxation implications when subdividing blocks. Would love to have a chat to you about your situation so feel free to contact me through my profile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am planning to buy land from a developer estate and then get a separate builder to construct the house. My plan is to start building as soon as the land gets titled. I am wondering which loans I can apply for. I am looking for a good rate.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-planning-to-buy-land-from-a-developer-estate-and-then-get-a-separate-builder-to-construct-the-house-my-plan-is-to-start-building-as-soon-as-the/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-planning-to-buy-land-from-a-developer-estate-and-then-get-a-separate-builder-to-construct-the-house-my-plan-is-to-start-building-as-soon-as-the/</guid>
      <description>This type of purchase would fall under a construction loan and is usually financed in two steps: buying the land then building the house. The loans can be arranged separately, but are generally bundled together for approval. The purchase of the land occurs as a standard mortgage. Then the building of the house operates as a construction loan where you can draw-down on an agreed amount to pay for each stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m buying a off the plan apartment through my SMSF. Purchase price is 600K. ( plus stamp etc) I&#39;ve put in 10% and anticipate completion in early 2018 ( maybe Feb) I&#39;m told the apartment has already increases approx 25% in value I want to know what loans are available to SMSF&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/im-buying-a-off-the-plan-apartment-through-my-smsf-purchase-price-is-600k-plus-stamp-etc-ive-put-in-10-and-anticipate-completion-in-early-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/im-buying-a-off-the-plan-apartment-through-my-smsf-purchase-price-is-600k-plus-stamp-etc-ive-put-in-10-and-anticipate-completion-in-early-2018/</guid>
      <description>Assuming your transaction has been structured appropriately (bare trust considerations), there are many factors (some below) to consider with SMSF lending. There are a limited number of options offering up to 80% LVR meaning that your SMSF will need to contribute funds representing at least 20% of the valuation on completion, which in itself could pose a problem as valuations may come in less than contract price. There may also be liquidity requirements meaning that the SMSF must have sufficient cash assets (post-completion) as a buffer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a current home owner and I am looking for a $10000 personal loan for home improvements.I don&#39;t have enough equity in my home that&#39;s why I need a personal loan.Could you please advise what lender would do personal loans and how quickly can a personal loan be approved by.I need the loan urgently.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-a-current-home-owner-and-i-am-looking-for-a-10000-personal-loan-for-home-improvementsi-dont-have-enough-equity-in-my-home-thats-why-i-need-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-a-current-home-owner-and-i-am-looking-for-a-10000-personal-loan-for-home-improvementsi-dont-have-enough-equity-in-my-home-thats-why-i-need-a/</guid>
      <description>There are numerous lenders that can provide unsecured finance within 24-48 hours. I would suggest that you are best to book an appointment with a broker to undertake a review of your financial circumstances. You may have more options available to you than you are currently aware of, including unlocking equity from your home with an up-to-date valuation, consolidating debt and accessing existing lines of credit, along with many other options that include exploring the wide variety of competitive personal loan products on the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a current home owner with a mortgage of $202,000. I am looking at re-financing my mortgage with lower repayments but would also like to burrow extra for minor house renovations. I don&#39;t have any other loans. I currently have a personal credit card with the credit limit of $9,000 (at the moment, my credit card debt is $500 as I don&#39;t really like using it unless it is for emergencies). I would like a loan that allows me to make extra repayments and have the ability to redraw if needed. I have been in my current job for 11months (started Oct 16) but can provide all necessary past financial documents if required. Please advise what the best option might be.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-a-current-home-owner-with-a-mortgage-of-202000-i-am-looking-at-refinancing-my-mortgage-with-lower-repayments-but-would-also-like-to-burrow-ex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-a-current-home-owner-with-a-mortgage-of-202000-i-am-looking-at-refinancing-my-mortgage-with-lower-repayments-but-would-also-like-to-burrow-ex/</guid>
      <description>We would be very happy to assist you with refinancing to reduce your repayments and at the same access some equity for some home improvements. As a general rule of thumb, if you have had your current loan for more than 2 years, then it is likely that you will be able to refinance at a better rate and access some loan features such as a line of credit and a redraw facility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a construction loan of approx. $310,000, have a block of land and owe approx. $130,000 on that with CBA and have a small personal loan of$ 29,000 also with CBA , my partner and I earn approx. $110,000 per year combined now the tricky thing is at the moment my partner is a undischarged bankrupt and wont be discharged until may next year. Are there any options out there for our circumstances or are we royally stuffed?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/looking-for-a-construction-loan-of-approx-310000-have-a-block-of-land-and-owe-approx-130000-on-that-with-cba-and-have-a-small-personal-loan-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/looking-for-a-construction-loan-of-approx-310000-have-a-block-of-land-and-owe-approx-130000-on-that-with-cba-and-have-a-small-personal-loan-of/</guid>
      <description>Your lending options are unfortunately limited with a co-borrower that has an undischarged bankruptcy. You really require the assistance of a broker who specialises in credit impaired finance. Not all brokers are specialists in this area so choose someone who declares this speciality, particularly if your loan requirements are time sensitive. Good luck and I hope you achieve your dream home ownership!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am interested in a home &amp; land package for 460,000 and can put in 40,000 deposit. So looking for 420,000 home loan. Gross Annual Income 84,000. First Time Home Buyer with no debts/no credit cards/no other loans. Two Dependents (Wife and Infant). Can I afford this property considering my borrowing power and Can I get less than 4.0% home loan interest rate?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-interested-in-a-home-land-package-for-460000-and-can-put-in-40000-deposit-so-looking-for-420000-home-loan-gross-annual-income-84000-firs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-interested-in-a-home-land-package-for-460000-and-can-put-in-40000-deposit-so-looking-for-420000-home-loan-gross-annual-income-84000-firs/</guid>
      <description>It sounds to me like you need a review of your financial circumstances to not only understand your borrowing power, but to also understand if a loan of this size will place you under financial distress. With 2 dependants, one being an infant, it is extremely important that you understand what loan amount you can afford, not necessary just what loan you can qualify for. With the Loan Value Ratio (LVR) you are looking at, you will likely be subject to Lenders Mortgage Insurance (LMI) which will add to the total cost of your loan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am looking at a block of flats to buy 4 of them. Is there a way that the seller can provide the deposit for example if the price is $270,000 have a price of $295,000 on the contract and him put up the $25k. Or any other way without him putting up the $25k upfront?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-looking-at-a-block-of-flats-to-buy-4-of-them-is-there-a-way-that-the-seller-can-provide-the-deposit-for-example-if-the-price-is-270000-have-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-looking-at-a-block-of-flats-to-buy-4-of-them-is-there-a-way-that-the-seller-can-provide-the-deposit-for-example-if-the-price-is-270000-have-a/</guid>
      <description>Are you saying you don&amp;rsquo;t want to put in a deposit or you don&amp;rsquo;t actually have any funds to put towards a deposit? Any lender is going to want to see that you have funds to complete the purchase, a deposit bond can assist if you don&amp;rsquo;t have access to the funds right now but will have the funds prior to settlement, e.g using equity from another property via refinance/equity release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m looking to buy my first home in the next few months, I will have a 5% deposit and earn around $115,000pa and 1 dependent. The problem is I have a default on my credit history (I feel its on there by mistake) If this can&#39;t be removed will that stop me from buying a property? The amount listed was for $395</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/im-looking-to-buy-my-first-home-in-the-next-few-months-i-will-have-a-5-deposit-and-earn-around-115000pa-and-1-dependent-the-problem-is-i-have-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/im-looking-to-buy-my-first-home-in-the-next-few-months-i-will-have-a-5-deposit-and-earn-around-115000pa-and-1-dependent-the-problem-is-i-have-a/</guid>
      <description>Firstly, congratulations on embarking on the home loan journey. It is a very exciting time but I understand that issue of a default can be stressful. A small default like you describe won&amp;rsquo;t necessarily stop you from getting a home loan approved, but there are things you can do to resolve it - as it is better to go in with a clean slate. Creditors will remove defaults if you can demonstrate they are wrong or you can make arrangements with them to pay it off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have a home loan with CBA but I am not on the title - my mother is on the title as well as the loan. She is a pensioner and I have always been paying the loan. I am finding it quite difficult to refinance as all banks need me to be on the title. I don&#39;t want to be on the title - just want to refinance - are there any lenders that would help me? </title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-have-a-home-loan-with-cba-but-i-am-not-on-the-title-my-mother-is-on-the-title-as-well-as-the-loan-she-is-a-pensioner-and-i-have-always-been-payin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-have-a-home-loan-with-cba-but-i-am-not-on-the-title-my-mother-is-on-the-title-as-well-as-the-loan-she-is-a-pensioner-and-i-have-always-been-payin/</guid>
      <description>This is indeed possible if you are happy to go jointly on the loan with your mother. You can still remain off the title. Unfortunately, there is no other way you will be able to refinance for her if you remain off the loan. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am 54, earn a reasonable income ($120k) per annum and my wife is 39 and earns under $50k, we have 5 kids and carry a bit of credit card debt, it&#39;s hard to save any money for a deposit, are there any no deposit products in the market these days? if not no deposit perhaps low deposit like 2% as they have in WA?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-54-earn-a-reasonable-income-120k-per-annum-and-my-wife-is-39-and-earns-under-50k-we-have-5-kids-and-carry-a-bit-of-credit-card-debt-its-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-54-earn-a-reasonable-income-120k-per-annum-and-my-wife-is-39-and-earns-under-50k-we-have-5-kids-and-carry-a-bit-of-credit-card-debt-its-h/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a busy man I see with 5 kids so good on you. Just to answer your question, it&amp;rsquo;s possible but you will need a really clean credit history as any loan you might take out will have to be approved by a Mortgage Insurer even after the lender says they will look at it. If you have a good rental payment history that helps and can be counted as genuine savings with certain lenders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HSBC Home Value Loan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/hsbc-home-value-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/hsbc-home-value-loan/</guid>
      <description>1. Features  [ ] Offset Account
 [x] Redraw Facility
 [x] Allow Extra Repayment
 [x] Allow Loan Increase
 [x] Split Loans
  2. Upfront Fees This is a fee that may be payable by the borrower to a lender prior to or at the application stage, of the lending process. An example of an upfront fee maybe an Application fee (while some may charge upfront, most do not), or Valuation fee (some lenders may charge, while others will cover this cost)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAB Choice Package Tailored 2 Years Fixed</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/nab-choice-package-tailored-2-years-fixed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/nab-choice-package-tailored-2-years-fixed/</guid>
      <description>1. Features  [ ] Offset Account
 [ ] Redraw Facility
 [ ] Allow Extra Repayment
 [ ] Allow Loan Increase
 [x] Split Loans
 [x] Interest In Advance
  2. Upfront Fees This is a fee that may be payable by the borrower to a lender prior to or at the application stage, of the lending process. An example of an upfront fee maybe an Application fee (while some may charge upfront, most do not), or Valuation fee (some lenders may charge, while others will cover this cost)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are there any banks that would be happy with the last 6 months of financials rather than just looking at the previous financial year as a whole?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/are-there-any-banks-that-would-be-happy-with-the-last-6-months-of-financials-rather-than-just-looking-at-the-previous-financial-year-as-a-whole/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/are-there-any-banks-that-would-be-happy-with-the-last-6-months-of-financials-rather-than-just-looking-at-the-previous-financial-year-as-a-whole/</guid>
      <description>There are only a couple of lenders that will accept 6 months history. No bank will look at last 6 months. They need minimum 16 &amp;amp; 17 financials. I will need more information on your situation to comment any further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current owner occupied home valued at $3.2M. Loan size $1.4M with 100% offset @ 3.71%. I have $700k in an offset account. 1. Is there a better rate home loan for my owner occupied home? 2. Is there possibility of borrowing more money for an investment property (with some of the deposits to be used from the offset account)? My salary income is $250k base a year. Wife not working. 1 dependant child.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/current-owner-occupied-home-valued-at-32m-loan-size-14m-with-100-offset-371-i-have-700k-in-an-offset-account-1-is-there-a-better-rate-ho/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/current-owner-occupied-home-valued-at-32m-loan-size-14m-with-100-offset-371-i-have-700k-in-an-offset-account-1-is-there-a-better-rate-ho/</guid>
      <description>You currently have a competitive rate on your home loan and you can certainly look to utilising the equity you have built up through your offset account and capital appreciation to invest in an investment property. I am a financial planner as well as being a mortgage broker located on the North Shore of Sydney. The strategies and structures are the key to you maximising your resources and I am happy to assist if you would like to contact me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Westpac Flexi First Option Home Loan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/westpac-flexi-first-option-home-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/westpac-flexi-first-option-home-loan/</guid>
      <description>1. Features  [ ] Offset Account
 [x] Redraw Facility
 [x] Allow Extra Repayment
 [x] Allow Loan Increase
 [x] Split Loans
  2. Upfront Fees This is a fee that may be payable by the borrower to a lender prior to or at the application stage, of the lending process. An example of an upfront fee maybe an Application fee (while some may charge upfront, most do not), or Valuation fee (some lenders may charge, while others will cover this cost)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve seen under some details that you can use the equity under a family members home to reduce LMI - can you use equity in property owned overseas in the UK</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ive-seen-under-some-details-that-you-can-use-the-equity-under-a-family-members-home-to-reduce-lmi-can-you-use-equity-in-property-owned-overseas-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ive-seen-under-some-details-that-you-can-use-the-equity-under-a-family-members-home-to-reduce-lmi-can-you-use-equity-in-property-owned-overseas-in/</guid>
      <description>Equity in an international asset is not acceptable security for Australian lenders. However, another effective means of freeing up funds to reduce or eliminate LMI is a ground approach to your overall financial situation. By taking a wholistic approach to your financial requirements and delving deeper into your circumstances, we can ensure that all facets of your financial situation are performing optimally. If you are servicing debts such as cars, credit cards, personal loans that affect your ability to save effectively and efficiently, a simple financial health check could provide you with the means to better service your loan, save a greater deposit and place you in better overall financial position prior to applying for a home loan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stamp Duty Calculator</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/stamp_duty_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/stamp_duty_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I would like to buy an investment property via a family trust structure. I will be the main person with borrowing capacity(20-30% deposit ready) and want to add two adult beneficiaries ( Parents )as well to the structure with no borrowing capacity .What are the loan options available and the rates in specific in your response kindly?I like to hear from someone servicing around Melbourne if possible in family trust loans for investment property</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-would-like-to-buy-an-investment-property-via-a-family-trust-structure-i-will-be-the-main-person-with-borrowing-capacity2030-deposit-ready-and-w/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-would-like-to-buy-an-investment-property-via-a-family-trust-structure-i-will-be-the-main-person-with-borrowing-capacity2030-deposit-ready-and-w/</guid>
      <description>I assume that you are operating under the professional advice of your accountant or lawyer given you are looking to structure your loan under a trust. You most certainly need the assistance of a broker who can effectively liaise with your accountant or lawyer to ascertain the most appropriate product for your specific needs, goals and circumstances. Most brokers can secure you a competitive interest rate on your loan, however I suggest you find one that will delve a little deeper into your situation to ensure you are recommended a loan that provides you with the best value rather the lowest rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am looking for the best deal for an investment loan. I have one residential property and one investment property at present. I would like to be contacted with the best deal for my situation.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-looking-for-the-best-deal-for-an-investment-loan-i-have-one-residential-property-and-one-investment-property-at-present-i-would-like-to-be-cont/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-looking-for-the-best-deal-for-an-investment-loan-i-have-one-residential-property-and-one-investment-property-at-present-i-would-like-to-be-cont/</guid>
      <description>The right investment home loan really depends on your particular financial goals. There are many different borrowing options and strategies available. Your investment loan should match your long-term financial goals and your broker should focus on maximising your borrowing power to achieve your investment goals faster. Most brokers can secure you a competitive interest rate on your loan, however I suggest you find one that will delve a little deeper into your situation to ensure you are recommended a loan that provides you with the best value rather than just the lowest rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a home loan for approx $500K. Earning good income and have an accountant&#39;s letter to confirm income. Is there a home loan product available?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/looking-for-a-home-loan-for-approx-500k-earning-good-income-and-have-an-accountants-letter-to-confirm-income-is-there-a-home-loan-product-availabl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/looking-for-a-home-loan-for-approx-500k-earning-good-income-and-have-an-accountants-letter-to-confirm-income-is-there-a-home-loan-product-availabl/</guid>
      <description>Most Lo Doc are maxed out at 80% - indicative rates 5.59% secured by owner occupied property and 5.59% investment. There are 90% loans - would be 6.5% +. Your accountant would need to sign off on the required income. For example -= to service requires income $80k if your single and with no other loans or credit cards - $86k with $10k credit card. Can work out specifics with more details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I currently have a residential home loan to the value of $500 000. We are currently looking at refinancing as our lender will not extend the interest only period of our loan. Current value of the property is in the order of $580 - $600k. We have had trouble refinancing as the serviceability calculator takes into account debt on principal &amp; Interest payments at a rate of %7.25. When our current debt repayments are interest only repayments at %4.19.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-currently-have-a-residential-home-loan-to-the-value-of-500-000-we-are-currently-looking-at-refinancing-as-our-lender-will-not-extend-the-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-currently-have-a-residential-home-loan-to-the-value-of-500-000-we-are-currently-looking-at-refinancing-as-our-lender-will-not-extend-the-interest/</guid>
      <description>I am guessing that your situation has changed since you first took out the loan. Unfortunately I think you are going to struggle to refinance if you are not able to service the debt according the lenders calculators. As part of responsible lending obligations both mortgage brokers and lenders need to ensure that you can manage repayments should interest rates rise. This is why we use higher rates in the lenders calculators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a first home buyer. I run my own business (freight truck driver) I clear $1000 per week after taxes. I have $50,000 saved for a deposit and am wondering how big of a home loan I would be able to get or any assistance.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-a-first-home-buyer-i-run-my-own-business-freight-truck-driver-i-clear-1000-per-week-after-taxes-i-have-50000-saved-for-a-deposit-and-am-wo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-a-first-home-buyer-i-run-my-own-business-freight-truck-driver-i-clear-1000-per-week-after-taxes-i-have-50000-saved-for-a-deposit-and-am-wo/</guid>
      <description>Great to see you have saved a significant deposit. The amount you can borrow is determined by your income and debt levels. As a first home buyer, you may also be eligible for First Home Owners Grant and exemptions from some government fees and charges. Being self-employed most lenders will require at least 2 years business financials. Would love to talk to you to gain a better understanding of your overall position and see how we can help you get into your own home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citibank Mortgage Plus Standard Variable Offset</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/citibank-mortgage-plus-standard-variable-offset/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 12:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/citibank-mortgage-plus-standard-variable-offset/</guid>
      <description>1. Features  [x] Offset Account
 [x] Redraw Facility
 [x] Allow Extra Repayment
 [x] Allow Loan Increase
 [x] Split Loans
  2. Upfront Fees This is a fee that may be payable by the borrower to a lender prior to or at the application stage, of the lending process. An example of an upfront fee maybe an Application fee (while some may charge upfront, most do not), or Valuation fee (some lenders may charge, while others will cover this cost)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I need to refinance for land. Loan for $315k, value $650k. In a family trust name. However, highly possible the loan will be paid out in the next few months as we hope to sell it. I am aware we will have penalty fees.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-need-to-refinance-for-land-loan-for-315k-value-650k-in-a-family-trust-name-however-highly-possible-the-loan-will-be-paid-out-in-the-next-few/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-need-to-refinance-for-land-loan-for-315k-value-650k-in-a-family-trust-name-however-highly-possible-the-loan-will-be-paid-out-in-the-next-few/</guid>
      <description>Why not consider private funding or the like, it&amp;rsquo;s a little more expensive, but very quick and very easy. No exit fees and the interest is prepaid with the loan proceeds. I hope that this helps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My partner (plus her mum, government job $62,000, her house valued at $500,000 and has $35,000 to pay plus $100,000 inheritance coming) and myself need to buy out her ex husbands share of the existing loan. The house was valued at $850,000 and we need to get approval for $500,000. We already had gotten a pre-approval from RAMS but that was based on the fact I was on Newstart allowance and has now run out. Myself and my partner are now both on Carers payment and allowance and I know RAMS didn&#39;t recognise this as income. Who does recognise carers payments? and would approve this.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/my-partner-plus-her-mum-government-job-62000-her-house-valued-at-500000-and-has-35000-to-pay-plus-100000-inheritance-coming-and-myself-nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/my-partner-plus-her-mum-government-job-62000-her-house-valued-at-500000-and-has-35000-to-pay-plus-100000-inheritance-coming-and-myself-nee/</guid>
      <description>There may be ways to work around the servicing of this issue. Primarily speaking there are lenders that look at carer&amp;rsquo;s allowance depending on the nature of it. Secondarily, it would be worthwhile to adjust perhaps your living situation for now if possible so that at least one of the properties can be used as an investment/rental. Let me know if you wish to explore this properly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am self employed, my partner works full time. Can we refinance to consolidate or credit card debt and personal loan ?? We are both 56 years of age and have a decent amount of equity in the house ??</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-self-employed-my-partner-works-full-time-can-we-refinance-to-consolidate-or-credit-card-debt-and-personal-loan-we-are-both-56-years-of-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-self-employed-my-partner-works-full-time-can-we-refinance-to-consolidate-or-credit-card-debt-and-personal-loan-we-are-both-56-years-of-age/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for your question. Providing you have sufficient equity in your property, then you should be able to consolidate your unsecured debt into the home loan. Some lenders may restrict the loan term once you are above the age of 55 but others are a little more flexible in regards to this, particularly if you can show a clear exit strategy. Being self employed, you have various options open to you such as low doc, one year business financials or the last two years of business financials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.what are requirements for showing genuine savings when the loan is being processed For a first home buyer having 10 percent deposit .Also how long does the statement of savings needs to be 2. Also I had a bad experience where in I had put an offer but the bank valuation came in lower than the contract price .What options do i have in that regard.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/what-are-requirements-for-showing-genuine-savings-when-the-loan-is-being-processed-for-a-first-home-buyer-having-10-percent-deposit-also-how-long-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/what-are-requirements-for-showing-genuine-savings-when-the-loan-is-being-processed-for-a-first-home-buyer-having-10-percent-deposit-also-how-long-d/</guid>
      <description>With a 10% deposit you dont need genuine savings at all. However if you have to go above 90% then there are other options available, such as rental payments etc. With regards to valuation - did you go to a bank direct - because brokers have access to various panel valuers and could easily get a second valuation or challenge the low valuation by way of additional documentation like comparable sales etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am an Australian Citizen and my husband has just applied for his permanent residency based on 820/801 spouse visa. Currently he is on a Bridging Visa A that will take him towards the 820 visa [in a couple of months] and then the 801. We would like to apply for a home loan with 5% deposit if we can as we would like to start building a new home shortly. It will also be our first home and we do qualify for FHOG. Would it be possible to secure a home loan?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-an-australian-citizen-and-my-husband-has-just-applied-for-his-permanent-residency-based-on-820801-spouse-visa-currently-he-is-on-a-bridging-vis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-am-an-australian-citizen-and-my-husband-has-just-applied-for-his-permanent-residency-based-on-820801-spouse-visa-currently-he-is-on-a-bridging-vis/</guid>
      <description>As Ditte has suggested you can get a loan but we will need more detail to confirm the amount. I have done a very similar one recently and the question is not just whether the Bank will accept your husband as a borrower but also if they will accept his income. At 95% loan there are not too many that do but some will. I am more than happy to go over this with you and explain your options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just wanting to know our options about the possibility of getting a home loan.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/just-wanting-to-know-our-options-about-the-possibility-of-getting-a-home-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/just-wanting-to-know-our-options-about-the-possibility-of-getting-a-home-loan/</guid>
      <description>What you would need to provide would be your Income - Expenses - Deposit (Equity or Family Guarantee). Income (all people who are borrowing) and details of what it is - salary - commission - family benefits etc. Expenses includes credit card limits, personal loans, car loans, HECS debt. Deposit - savings or any current property - any family member who can guarantee security so you dont need to save for a deposit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMP Professional Package Rariable Rate</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/amp-professional-package-rariable-rate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 12:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/amp-professional-package-rariable-rate/</guid>
      <description>1. Features  [x] Offset Account
 [x] Redraw Facility
 [x] Allow Extra Repayment
 [x] Allow Loan Increase
 [x] Split Loans
  2. Upfront Fees This is a fee that may be payable by the borrower to a lender prior to or at the application stage, of the lending process. An example of an upfront fee maybe an Application fee (while some may charge upfront, most do not), or Valuation fee (some lenders may charge, while others will cover this cost)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it possible to use the FHOG to help make up a deposit or should I save more? Any advice on the following stats would be welcome. STATS: Couple - stable combined income 200K - 250K, debt (car/cards - currently being paid off fast) 40K, excellent credit history. Only a low deposit saved of 10K.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/is-it-possible-to-use-the-fhog-to-help-make-up-a-deposit-or-should-i-save-more-any-advice-on-the-following-stats-would-be-welcome-only-a-low-deposit-saved-of-10k/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/is-it-possible-to-use-the-fhog-to-help-make-up-a-deposit-or-should-i-save-more-any-advice-on-the-following-stats-would-be-welcome-only-a-low-deposit-saved-of-10k/</guid>
      <description>Generally lenders will require 5% of the total contract/purchase price as genuine savings. This means that it would need to be tracked back at least 3 months with a regular pattern rather than erratic lump sums. There are a few lenders who will accept rental history in leau of savings but the rental contract must be via a licensed real estate agent. The FHOG is not counted as genuine savings by lenders but is used at the drawdown of the construction loan to assist with the total cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are looking to refinance to consolidate and release equity. Upon applying we discovered my partner has a paid default -credit card $3000 from @3 years ago and had been late on some recent payments in last 6 months on current cards but up to date and not on credit record. We have been approved by one of the big4 for our home loan and credit cards but not the extra we wanted with sub 3.9% rate . Property @$650,000 value - current loan $225k and @$22 on cards want to release $75k approx for improvements and another purpose.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/we-are-looking-to-refinance-to-consolidate-and-release-equity-upon-applying-we-discovered-my-partner-has-a-paid-default-credit-card-3000-from-3-ye/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/we-are-looking-to-refinance-to-consolidate-and-release-equity-upon-applying-we-discovered-my-partner-has-a-paid-default-credit-card-3000-from-3-ye/</guid>
      <description>We have a number of lenders that will consider your application and cash out requirements. Rates from 3.74% subject to standard lender approval process. As part of our service, I will conduct a detailed review of your current situation and finance requirements to ensure the best possible solution is presented to you. Your decision to engage Clark Finance Group will not only maximise your results, but it will also give you the peace of mind of knowing we will find you the most competitive finance package that will meet your needs, and we will facilitate the process swiftly and professionally from start to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra Repayment Calculators</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/extra_repayment_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/extra_repayment_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I want to pay down my home loan as fast I can. Can a broker help me with a finance stratgey that involves in property investment ? I&#39;ve read about people paying off their home in 5 years is this possible? Should I see financial planner or can broker help me with this? I own 430K dwelling owe 380K my wife and I have combined income of 110K.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/i-want-to-pay-down-my-home-loan-as-fast-i-can-can-a-broker-help-me-with-a-finance-stratgey-that-involves-in-property-investment-ive-read-about-peo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/i-want-to-pay-down-my-home-loan-as-fast-i-can-can-a-broker-help-me-with-a-finance-stratgey-that-involves-in-property-investment-ive-read-about-peo/</guid>
      <description>We work closely with many of our clients to help them pay off their home in the fastest possible time, invest in property while minimizing taxation and growing their wealth for their family and their future. We have seen people pay their homes off in 5 -10 years but it does rely on numerous factors such as increasing capital growth rates, equity, discipline and particular loan structures and products. More than happy to take you through the process and develop an customised strategy for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BankWest Equaliser Home Loan Variable 3 year introductory rate</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/bankwest-equaliser-home-loan-variable-3-year-introductory-rate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 12:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/bankwest-equaliser-home-loan-variable-3-year-introductory-rate/</guid>
      <description>1. Features  [ ] Offset Account
 [x] Redraw Facility
 [x] Allow Extra Repayment
 [x] Allow Loan Increase
 [x] Split Loans
  2. Upfront Fees This is a fee that may be payable by the borrower to a lender prior to or at the application stage, of the lending process. An example of an upfront fee maybe an Application fee (while some may charge upfront, most do not), or Valuation fee (some lenders may charge, while others will cover this cost)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loan Comparison Calculators</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/loan_comparison_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/loan_comparison_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ING Orange Advantage Home Loan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/ing-orange-advantage-home-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 12:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/ing-orange-advantage-home-loan/</guid>
      <description>1. Features  [x] Offset Account
 [x] Redraw Facility
 [x] Allow Extra Repayment
 [x] Allow Loan Increase
 [x] Split Loans
  2. Upfront Fees This is a fee that may be payable by the borrower to a lender prior to or at the application stage, of the lending process. An example of an upfront fee maybe an Application fee (while some may charge upfront, most do not), or Valuation fee (some lenders may charge, while others will cover this cost)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St George Basic Home Loan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/st-george-basic-home-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 12:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/homeloan/st-george-basic-home-loan/</guid>
      <description>1. Features  [ ] Offset Account
 [x] Redraw Facility
 [x] Allow Extra Repayment
 [x] Allow Loan Increase
 [x] Split Loans
  2. Upfront Fees This is a fee that may be payable by the borrower to a lender prior to or at the application stage, of the lending process. An example of an upfront fee maybe an Application fee (while some may charge upfront, most do not), or Valuation fee (some lenders may charge, while others will cover this cost)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mortgage Switching Calculators</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/mortgage_switching_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/mortgage_switching_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split Loan Calculators</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/split_loan_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/split_loan_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interest Only Mortgage Calculator</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/interest_only_mortgage_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/interest_only_mortgage_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rent vs Buy Calculator</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/rent_vs_buy_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/rent_vs_buy_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Income Tax Calculator</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/income_tax_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/calculator/income_tax_calculator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Chong</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/aaron-chong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/aaron-chong/</guid>
      <description> Lawyer from University of Melbourne Former investment banker Property developer Property finance specialist
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Sainsbury</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/aaron-sainsbury/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/aaron-sainsbury/</guid>
      <description> Aaron Sainsbury has been an enthusiastic advocate for financial literacy throughout his working life
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abdul Eldib</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/abdul-eldib/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/abdul-eldib/</guid>
      <description> At Fast Repay Home Loan we help you find the best interest rate
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Van Der Helm</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/adam-van-der-helm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/adam-van-der-helm/</guid>
      <description> With over 15 years in combined banking and financial services I can find the the right loan for you. It is important to match your individual situation to the right lender so that I can get your finance approved&amp;hellip; With over 30 lenders available on our panel there is always an option
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aditya Dhawan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/aditya-dhawan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/aditya-dhawan/</guid>
      <description> Having completed his Master of Accounting from Edith Cowan University
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adrian Kutzner</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/adrian-kutzner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/adrian-kutzner/</guid>
      <description> Adrian has a strong knowledge of property finance and the investment market through his years as a property investor. With a strong passion for helping first home buyers enter the property market through professional knowledge and encouragement
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adrian Signore</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/adrian-signore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/adrian-signore/</guid>
      <description> Helping clients find the perfect loan is more to me than a job. I have a degree in commerce and went into mortgage broking because I could see the opportunity that existed. I am extremely analytical and get a little too much enjoyment from numbers and loan comparisons! I work around the clock and will always answer the phone. When I&amp;rsquo;m not broking I am at the football
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adrian Vanderkley</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/adrian-vanderkley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/adrian-vanderkley/</guid>
      <description> My name is Adrian Vanderkley. I??m the founder of Vanda Corporation Pty Ltd; which was established in July 2005
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adriano Tassone</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/adriano-tassone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/adriano-tassone/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ajay Krishnan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ajay-krishnan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ajay-krishnan/</guid>
      <description> I help you to make the right decision about your Home Loan. Whether it is for your first house or growing your property portfolio or to simply consolidate debts
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albert Waldron</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/albert-waldron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/albert-waldron/</guid>
      <description> Albert is extremely experienced in the finance industry with over 14 years experience. The last seven of these involving clients with complicated structures and sophisticated investors. He has a passion for ensuring clients build a property portfolio that can be grown as quickly and safely as possible. In addition to holding over 40 lender accreditation s
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Filipovic</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/alex-filipovic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/alex-filipovic/</guid>
      <description> I am a franchise owner of Nectar Mortgages &amp;amp; have been involved in finance in the banking &amp;amp; finance broking industry for many years. Qualifications include a Diploma of Financial Planning
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alicia James</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/alicia-james/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/alicia-james/</guid>
      <description> Everyone is different and you cannot cookie cut a mortgage. I can guarantee dedicated and tailored solutions for all my clients
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allan Cresser</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/allan-cresser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/allan-cresser/</guid>
      <description> I have over 13 years experience in the Mortgage Broking industry. Previously I operated a retail business
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allan Faint</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/allan-faint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/allan-faint/</guid>
      <description> Have been a Mortgage Broker for 15 years. With a lending panel of well over 30 lenders. Can also offer loans to MBA members through MBA Finance. loans offered are home and investment loans
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allan Houliston</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/allan-houliston/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/allan-houliston/</guid>
      <description> The founder of Aisling Financial
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alun Vernals</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/alun-vernals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/alun-vernals/</guid>
      <description>Finance 365 is a new company with an old fashioned focus on great customer service and ensuring that we can make your road to home ownership nice and smooth. We&amp;rsquo;ll endeavor to give you only genuine advice that is right for your situation to ensure the best possible outcome. The brokerage has won a number of awards which you can view at www.finance365.com.au On a personal level I started as a finance broker back in 2001.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amanda Bevilacqua</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/amanda-bevilacqua/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/amanda-bevilacqua/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amanda Tucker</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/amanda-tucker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/amanda-tucker/</guid>
      <description> I have been in the financial services industry since 1995. My experience includes dealing with clients in the personal
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amit Gupta</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/amit-gupta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/amit-gupta/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amit Singh</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/amit-singh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/amit-singh/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amy Ferguson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/amy-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/amy-ferguson/</guid>
      <description> Being an investor myself
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Barbazza</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-barbazza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-barbazza/</guid>
      <description> Hi
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Black</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-black/</guid>
      <description> I have found my experience lends itself to deal with life&amp;rsquo;s curve balls
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew De Marco</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-de-marco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-de-marco/</guid>
      <description> &amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo;Here to guide you every step of the way
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Goggin</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-goggin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-goggin/</guid>
      <description>As the practice principle at Key Asset Group I am passionate about coaching my clients on how to implement financial strategies that make a real positive difference to their financial results. Helping them to do this in a way that is easy to understand and apply. Nothing gives me more pleasure than seeing clients own their home and create a financially better lifestyle for themselves and their family. I love seeing them achieve their goals faster</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Lunt</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-lunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-lunt/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Paterson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-paterson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-paterson/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Patterson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-patterson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-patterson/</guid>
      <description> I am an experienced finance broker with over 14 years in the mortgage industry. I am able to assist you with home loans
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Peake</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-peake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-peake/</guid>
      <description> Your first contact for all your mortgage and car finance requirements. Over 16 years experience and access to over 30 lenders. I pride my myself on being responsive to ALL my customers requirements
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Rowlands</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-rowlands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-rowlands/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Walker</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-walker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-walker/</guid>
      <description> I have been involved in finance and business my whole life. Growing up
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Walmsley</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-walmsley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/andrew-walmsley/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angelo Benedetti</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/angelo-benedetti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/angelo-benedetti/</guid>
      <description> With access to a huge number of lenders and 23 years industry experience
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angelo La Selva</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/angelo-la-selva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/angelo-la-selva/</guid>
      <description> Before you apply for a loan consider the benefits of using a qualified finance &amp;amp; mortgage broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anita Sareen</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/anita-sareen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/anita-sareen/</guid>
      <description> Long standing banking experience with dedication to assist clients in fulfilling their dreams into a reality. I strongly believe in helping clients achieving their goals and following the path of this journey together. My top priority is to find the best structure and save you dollars.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AnnMarie-Bosco</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/annmarie-bosco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/annmarie-bosco/</guid>
      <description> After spending my childhood on the family farm on Eyre Peninsula
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Del Baglivo</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/anthony-del-baglivo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/anthony-del-baglivo/</guid>
      <description> With over 8 years of lending experience and now as a Finance &amp;amp; Mortgage Broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Hong</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/anthony-hong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/anthony-hong/</guid>
      <description> Anthony has the ability to provide a number of proposals through a panel of lenders without the limiting factors of a single lender. With the clients?? needs and ambitions front of mind
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anthony O&#39;Flynn</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/anthony-oflynn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/anthony-oflynn/</guid>
      <description> I have been working in the finance industry for over 30 years
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Ryan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/anthony-ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/anthony-ryan/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antony Blanch</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/antony-blanch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/antony-blanch/</guid>
      <description>I have been a finance and mortgage broker since 1997. Being a Liberty Adviser provides free thinking options and client focused solutions. I have extensive experience in all areas of finance and love helping others through the options I can provide. I pride myself on providing outstanding service and keeping clients up to date at every stage in the process. My excellence in service was acknowledged when I was awarded the 2017 Liberty Customer Service Adviser award</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anubhuti Kapoor</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/anubhuti-kapoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/anubhuti-kapoor/</guid>
      <description>At Star Home Loan &amp;amp; Investment our job and passion is to service help you with the expert advice for your home loan. With over 30 specialized lenders our aim is to provide you the outstanding consultation that suits your financial situation at its best. *Our services are at no cost to you * assisting customer Australia wide on any type of loan Keeping the process simple and easy RP Data at no cost to our customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aron Cardona</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/aron-cardona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/aron-cardona/</guid>
      <description> As a mortgage broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Lim</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/arthur-lim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/arthur-lim/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;Dual languages English and Indonesian. First home buyer specialist. Investor and debt consolidation specialist.&amp;rdquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azm Khan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/azm-khan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/azm-khan/</guid>
      <description> I am passionate about helping people achieve their financial goals and realise that finding a suitable home loan is sometimes a daunting task that it shouldn t be. My aim is to hold your hand and guide you through the whole process of finding the best home loan for your situation so you can focus on what really matters to you
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beatrice Baumann</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/beatrice-baumann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/beatrice-baumann/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belinda Gibson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/belinda-gibson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/belinda-gibson/</guid>
      <description> More than 15 years Commercial Banking experience has afforded her the scope you expect from an influential Company Director. Specialising in Property
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belinda Sukoski</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/belinda-sukoski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/belinda-sukoski/</guid>
      <description> Your Finance Coach that will help you every step of the way. If your looking at purchasing a New Home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Adih</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ben-adih/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ben-adih/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Chen</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ben-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ben-chen/</guid>
      <description> Ben is the Director of Regno Finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Gardner</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ben-gardner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ben-gardner/</guid>
      <description> Based on the beautiful Mornington Peninsula. I am the Director and Senior Mortgage Broker of New Patch Mortgage Brokers. I am also a Qualified CPA Accountant and member of the Mortgage and Finance Association of Australia. We are passionate about our friendly refreshing approach to customer service and are committed to helping all of our clients fulfil their lending and investment goals.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benjamin Edwards</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/benjamin-edwards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/benjamin-edwards/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benjamin Lowe</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/benjamin-lowe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/benjamin-lowe/</guid>
      <description> I have been in the finance industry for over 15 years with 3 years as a mortgage broker. I am passionate to get the best deal for my clients and offer the highest quality service during and after the deal. I have built a strong network of like minded professionals in areas of conveyancing
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benjamin Whyte</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/benjamin-whyte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/benjamin-whyte/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Kyne</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/bernie-kyne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/bernie-kyne/</guid>
      <description> I am passionate about helping clients reach their home ownership dreams. With 4 years as a mortgage broker and previously as an accountant for over 25 years my strong background in finance gives me the knowledge and life experience to match your unique financial situation to the specific lending requirements of lenders. Whether you??re a first home buyer
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bez Esquivel</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/bez-esquivel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/bez-esquivel/</guid>
      <description> With many years of experience in the home/investment loan and business finance space
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blair Turner</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/blair-turner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/blair-turner/</guid>
      <description>Based in Hobart CBD I cover the south of the state with Danielle looking after the north. I am the Lending Adviser at The Premium Business Group . I have over 20 years of experience working for the banks &amp;amp; for myself. My goal is to work with you in finding a loan that best suits your needs from the hundreds of different options that are available in the market place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonny Tong</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/bonny-tong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/bonny-tong/</guid>
      <description> Based in Perth
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brad Dawson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/brad-dawson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/brad-dawson/</guid>
      <description> #1 NT/SA
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bradley Erickson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/bradley-erickson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/bradley-erickson/</guid>
      <description> I am a customer focused broker with a proven track record of delivering quality services to my clients. I will assist you to find a loan that not only meets your needs
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brady Henley</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/brady-henley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/brady-henley/</guid>
      <description> I am proud to be part of the One Plus One Financial Solutions team; together we facilitate
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bren Rodda</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/bren-rodda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/bren-rodda/</guid>
      <description> I am the Director of Loan Market Darwin and have been Mortgage Broking for over 9 year. I was MPA Magazines Number 1 broker in the NT for 2015
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brendan Barker</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/brendan-barker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/brendan-barker/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;m your Home Financing Specialist and I specialise in helping families to get their finances under control
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brent Tonkin</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/brent-tonkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/brent-tonkin/</guid>
      <description>I??m a Finance Consultant based in Echuca and I pride myself on delivering the best options to suit my customers?? needs. I have proven credentials with over 10 years experience in the Financial and Credit services industries. I now operate as an independent agent to financial institutions and facilitate and negotiate the best deal for my clients. I do this by seeking a thorough understanding of my clients?? financial needs and goals</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brenton Parsons</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/brenton-parsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/brenton-parsons/</guid>
      <description> My focus is to offer reliable
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brian Bratich</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/brian-bratich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/brian-bratich/</guid>
      <description> I am a Chartered Accountant that has worked in banking for the last 9 years and held roles in corporate finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brian Taylor</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/brian-taylor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/brian-taylor/</guid>
      <description> I am a dedicated professional committed to getting my clients the best deal out there. I love what I do as I get to meet lots of people and enjoy building ongoing relationships. I specialise in helping people pay off their mortgage in half the time.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulelwa Freer</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/bulelwa-freer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/bulelwa-freer/</guid>
      <description> Wealth creation
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carl Violeta</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/carl-violeta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/carl-violeta/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Brannon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/carlos-brannon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/carlos-brannon/</guid>
      <description> Whether you need a loan for your dream house
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caroline Pollard</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/caroline-pollard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/caroline-pollard/</guid>
      <description> Director of Bayside Finance Solutions Elwood
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caroline Shapley</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/caroline-shapley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/caroline-shapley/</guid>
      <description> I take a personalised approach to lending
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Byrne</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/carolyn-byrne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/carolyn-byrne/</guid>
      <description> With 15 years experience as a finance broker in Perth
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Sutherland</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/carolyn-sutherland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/carolyn-sutherland/</guid>
      <description> My clients see me as a straight shooter
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catherine Smith</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/catherine-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/catherine-smith/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherie Knock</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/cherie-knock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/cherie-knock/</guid>
      <description> I am motivated by seeing my clients achieve their financial best. I pride myself on exceptional customer service that will see you become a client for life. No matter if your goal is focused on saving
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Coyne</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/chris-coyne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/chris-coyne/</guid>
      <description>After 15 years as a professional Soccer player in England and representing the Socceroos it was time to for a new career and to try and chase a different goal . After 3 and a half years as a broker I am starting to see how rewarding assisting people into their new homes and saving them money via refinancing current loans. I am a part of the Finance 365 team that has won numerous awards and you can go to www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Donnelly</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/chris-donnelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/chris-donnelly/</guid>
      <description> I have been working in the Financial Services industry since 1989 and started lending in 1993. I have experience in the following areas: Home Loans
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Foster-Ramsay</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/chris-foster-ramsay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/chris-foster-ramsay/</guid>
      <description> Chris Foster-Ramsay is a multi-award winning finance and mortgage broker with over 15 years of lending experience. Based in the south-east and with Clients far and wide
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hientz</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/chris-hientz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/chris-hientz/</guid>
      <description> I have a passion for helping businesses and individuals achieve their financial goals and get the best deal at the same time. Since 2003
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Mills</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/chris-mills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/chris-mills/</guid>
      <description>I have 14 years experience in finance and I am a multiple award winner at AFG. We at Network HQ pride ourselves in providing our clients with the very best services with our team of professional advisors to insure that you have the correct structure. Our focus is to provide services to meet your timeframes and negotiate the lowest interest rates available across all of our lenders. We can assist with: - Home and Investment loans - Refinance - Personal - Business - Car - SMSF We look forward to providing you with the required knowledge and skills so that you can confidently make informed decisions and take control of your financial position</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Polatsidis</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/chris-polatsidis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/chris-polatsidis/</guid>
      <description> We are experts in researching and matching a selection of loan products to your individual requirements. Over 25 years of helping people achieve their dreams
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Straw</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/chris-straw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/chris-straw/</guid>
      <description> I have over 30 years experience within the financial services industry in both lending and business development roles with some of Australia&amp;rsquo;s major financial institutions. My passion and commitment is to assist my clients in achieving your financial objectives. I take seriously my responsibility in being an advocate for my clients and helping you improve your financial position and achieve your goals.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christian Stevens</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/christian-stevens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/christian-stevens/</guid>
      <description> Christian Stevens is a leading property finance specialist strategically aligned to the real estate industry. Christian works as a senior mortgage broker at the multi-award winning Shore Financial
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christine Hornery</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/christine-hornery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/christine-hornery/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Brown</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-brown/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The team at New Vision Financial Services have access to over 40 different lenders, giving you more flexibility when making a decision. Our consultants have had extensive experience within the banking, financial and corporate sector. At New Vision Financial Services we specialise in finance lending for home, investment, business, commercial, asset, debtor and many other requirements. As New Vision Financial Services has progressed, we have developed strong relationships with professional service providers such as; Financial Planners, Accountants, Settlement Agents, Leasing &amp;amp; Equipment Providers, Debt Management Specialists and many more to allow our clients access to a complete suite of services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Gerreyn</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-gerreyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-gerreyn/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Jonson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-jonson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-jonson/</guid>
      <description> I have the experience to deal with all facets of finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Sales</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-sales/</guid>
      <description>I am the director of Finance Warehouse and have been in the industry for over 10 years. Double Degree honors in Finance and Economics as well as being nominated in the top 10 new brokers in Australia when first starting. in 2017 Voted the best Commercial Broker by my aggregation. I have access to over 20 lenders and have premium access to many of the majors meaning faster turn around times for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinton Burnes</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/clinton-burnes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/clinton-burnes/</guid>
      <description> I am very passionate about saving clients money and reduce their loan term on their home loan/s and working with them throughout the life of the loan to reach their desired goals and to make sure you are being kept up to date with changes in the market.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collins Mayaki</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/collins-mayaki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/collins-mayaki/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conrad Palmer</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/conrad-palmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/conrad-palmer/</guid>
      <description> An experienced finance manager and mortgage broker on the Gold Coast
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coral Campbell</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/coral-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/coral-campbell/</guid>
      <description> I am absolutely committed to my clients through a high level of service and advice. I assist clients Australia wide. My service is at no cost to you while keeping the process easy; hassle free and gaining loan approval as soon as possible. I will always be available to answer any questions or concerns. My commitment is to work hard for you and with you
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corey Iredale</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/corey-iredale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/corey-iredale/</guid>
      <description> We are a locally owned an operated Mortgage Broker company
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Costas Louras</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/costas-louras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/costas-louras/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cristian Tihon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/cristian-tihon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/cristian-tihon/</guid>
      <description> With thirteen years finance experience across a broad range of areas
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D&#39;Avery Pillay</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/davery-pillay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/davery-pillay/</guid>
      <description> As a mortgage broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damien Minissale</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/damien-minissale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/damien-minissale/</guid>
      <description> Experienced Broker with over a Decade in the Finance Industry. Specialising in Lending Product and Policy Knowledge. You will find me an invaluable source of information for Purchases and Refinancing . First Home Buyers Specialist. I negotiate with Lenders directly on your behalf. Non obligatory Home visits or visit my office if your prefer. I do not charge a fee for my services. 25 Lenders
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Casey</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-casey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-casey/</guid>
      <description> Hello future customers! I am very excited to work together to reach your financials goals. I have been involved in the finance industry for over seven years originally as a brokers assistant and then from 2012 a fully qualified finance consultant. I am hard working and committed to finding solutions for clients financial needs
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Finn</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-finn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-finn/</guid>
      <description> Daniel is an experienced mortgage broker. His role as a professional mortgage adviser is to assist his clients to find the right loan/lender for your circumstances. Daniel has access to over 30 lenders to ensure he can present a wide range of options for you whether your an investor
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Gaunt</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-gaunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-gaunt/</guid>
      <description> Sydney Finance Services is a Finance Broker based in Sutherland Shire
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Oconnor</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-oconnor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-oconnor/</guid>
      <description> Local resident with a business background
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Reid</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-reid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-reid/</guid>
      <description> Emanate Finance is your first stop for all things finance. Founded by Daniel Reid in an effort to fill a gap in the market place
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Roscio</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-roscio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-roscio/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Venpin</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-venpin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/daniel-venpin/</guid>
      <description> I am a highly dedicated broker who will go &amp;lsquo;above and beyond&amp;rsquo; to ensure you get the very best of advice and support when it comes to your property finance. I do the &amp;lsquo;heavy lifting&amp;rsquo; on your behalf
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniela Greening</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/daniela-greening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/daniela-greening/</guid>
      <description> Based in Melbourne
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danny Lang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/danny-lang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/danny-lang/</guid>
      <description> Danny Lang has a passion for helping his clients achieve their investment goals in this ever-changing market. Known for being reliable
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darby Franklin</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/darby-franklin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/darby-franklin/</guid>
      <description> My aim is to find you a loan that not only meets your requirements
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darren Mccormack</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/darren-mccormack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/darren-mccormack/</guid>
      <description> Darren ensures he makes the home loan application process as simple and effortless as possible. Darren is a strong advocate for seeking a pre-approval upfront
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darren Roach</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/darren-roach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/darren-roach/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dave Rase</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/dave-rase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/dave-rase/</guid>
      <description> I have been a mortgage broker since 2004 and have helped hundreds of people find loans that are best suitable for them when purchasing a property. If it is your first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Chen</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/david-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/david-chen/</guid>
      <description> Excels as a business strategist and mortgage broker. Holds a commerce degree
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Cosgrove</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/david-cosgrove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/david-cosgrove/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Goode</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/david-goode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/david-goode/</guid>
      <description> Have been in the finance industry for many years and pride myself on delivering quality service and products. Was a former Bank Manager for over 25 years. I provide home loans
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Nassoor</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/david-nassoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/david-nassoor/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Randall</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/david-randall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/david-randall/</guid>
      <description> Avaibale 7 days a week
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Sharpe</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/david-sharpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/david-sharpe/</guid>
      <description> I assist individuals and small businesses to obtain finance for whatever purpose they require
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Smith</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/david-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/david-smith/</guid>
      <description> David Smith trading as Mortgage Seekers Australia operates under Australia Credit Licence No 482074 of New Beginning Group (Australia) which I am the sole director. With over 43 years in banking &amp;amp; finance including a Major Australian Bank
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Webb</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/david-webb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/david-webb/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daxa Mistry</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/daxa-mistry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/daxa-mistry/</guid>
      <description> I am a Sydney-based finance manager with Anne Street Partners- an Australian financial services provider
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debra Burnett</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/debra-burnett/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/debra-burnett/</guid>
      <description> I have been in banking and finance since 1988
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dee Britton</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/dee-britton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/dee-britton/</guid>
      <description> I have worked in the finance industry since 1994. I pride myself on providing a personalised and streamlined service to my valued clients that caters to their current and long term financial goals. I have access to highly competitive products and can often negotiate a better deal with your bank than you can. I can also help you with your equipment finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deon Kruger</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/deon-kruger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/deon-kruger/</guid>
      <description> Helping people and families achieve their dream of home ownership and get the right deal from the very start. I am here to help you negotiate the right deal and avoid unnecessary costs. If you want to own your home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Derik Karamian</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/derik-karamian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/derik-karamian/</guid>
      <description> Australian Loan House is an independent Sydney based mortgage Broking Company created to help everyday Australians prosper and grow. Australian Loan House has established partnerships and relationships with over 30 of Australia??s largest banks
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dhaval Thakkar</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/dhaval-thakkar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/dhaval-thakkar/</guid>
      <description> After completing my MBA in Finance back in 2010
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dida Zhuang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/dida-zhuang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/dida-zhuang/</guid>
      <description> As an registered mortgage broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dim Mastoros</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/dim-mastoros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/dim-mastoros/</guid>
      <description> My commitment to you extends far beyond settlement of your loan. Whether it be your first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ditte Westbury</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ditte-westbury/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ditte-westbury/</guid>
      <description> Obtaining finance should be easy and seamless
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dom Dzakula</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/dom-dzakula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/dom-dzakula/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domarina Pireh</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/domarina-pireh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/domarina-pireh/</guid>
      <description>We at The Lending Circle are motivated by helping our customers achieve the best rates and products. We also assist in showing our customers how to pay off their loans in a shorter period so they can enjoy owning their property sooner. We have been in the finance and property industry since 1993 so we are highly experienced. Since the finance industry is constantly changing we are also constantly doing continuous professional development with the lenders so we are always up to date with all the different lenders products</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dominic Trimboli</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/dominic-trimboli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/dominic-trimboli/</guid>
      <description> I work as a mortgage broker in Payneham and pride myself on getting my clients the best possible loan for their situation. Extremely passionate about this industry as it enables the consumer to scan the entire market for the right fit
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eddy Poh</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/eddy-poh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/eddy-poh/</guid>
      <description>Eddy is the mortgage consultant with Australian Loan Professionals and has held roles in both Accounting and Finance Industry since 2001. Eddy is passionate about Mortgage Broking because he has the opportunity to provide tailored solutions to help clients reach their lifestyle goals and financial potential through wealth creation strategies. Eddy holds a . Bachelor of Accounting . Advanced Diploma of Financial Planning . Certificate IV in Financial Services (Finance / Mortgage Broking) .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edward Wingate</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/edward-wingate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/edward-wingate/</guid>
      <description> Edward brings a wealth of experience and enthusiasm to his role as Regional Manager and Broker at Nectar. Not only has he held positions in some of the top global and national real estate companies
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elia Theodore</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/elia-theodore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/elia-theodore/</guid>
      <description> Having worked in two major brokerages and as a private banker I have developed the skills and industry knowledge necessary to ensure the best possible outcome for my clients
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elliot Smith</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/elliot-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/elliot-smith/</guid>
      <description> Elliot has worked for 3 well known banks in his finance career being Bankwest
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elvis Adamson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/elvis-adamson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/elvis-adamson/</guid>
      <description> ELCOL Mortgage Brokers is a focussed brokerage providing quality mortgage broking services
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emma Johansson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/emma-johansson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/emma-johansson/</guid>
      <description> Buying a home or an investment property can be the most rewarding albeit stressful time in your life. I aim to take the worry and pressure of applying for finance and offer a quality and efficient process that will enable you to focus on the positives.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emmanuel Guignard</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/emmanuel-guignard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/emmanuel-guignard/</guid>
      <description> Emmanuel Guignard is Loanscope??s Senior Mortgage Broker and Director. Emmanuel founded Loanscope after many years as a relationship manager at CBA and Bank of Melbourne
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eric Dong</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/eric-dong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/eric-dong/</guid>
      <description> EK Mortgage focus on residential and commercial loan business. We do the legwork
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eric Ta</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/eric-ta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/eric-ta/</guid>
      <description> With over 15 years in the industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Erkan Karacan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/erkan-karacan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/erkan-karacan/</guid>
      <description> Senior Financial Adviser and Mortgage Adviser with over 10 years experience in Financial Services and significant stints at multi-national organisations such as ANZ
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Erol Balci</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/erol-balci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/erol-balci/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farzin Hesari</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/farzin-hesari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/farzin-hesari/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First name Last name</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/first-name-last-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/first-name-last-name/</guid>
      <description> Quote
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fran Jerome</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/fran-jerome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/fran-jerome/</guid>
      <description> Everything I do is to put my clients in a better financial position than they were previously. I am a CPA and brings to the fore 2 decades of experience in the field of banking and finance so that my clients get the appropriate loan structuring and mortgage. Refinancing and Debt consolidations are my core competencies. My final reward
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frank Tamayo</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/frank-tamayo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/frank-tamayo/</guid>
      <description> Finding the right solution to fit your finance needs is my utmost priority. I will not only take the time to understand your financial situation and aspirations
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frazer Martin</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/frazer-martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/frazer-martin/</guid>
      <description> Mortgage Broker / Financial Consultant AFB
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gabriel Cobb-Diamond</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/gabriel-cobb-diamond/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/gabriel-cobb-diamond/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gareth Thomas</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/gareth-thomas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/gareth-thomas/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gary Fabian</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/gary-fabian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/gary-fabian/</guid>
      <description>Precision Advisory is a privately owned Gold Coast financial services consultancy aligned with all the major Australian based financial institutions. We implement sound and practical finance and wealth-creation strategies that are proven to achieve results for our valued clients. We live in one of the most affluent and beautiful countries in the world and it??s a sad fact that the majority of people will be reliant on the government pension when it comes time for them to retire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gary Lewis</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/gary-lewis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/gary-lewis/</guid>
      <description> I CARE about my Clients and love that I have been able to improve their lives. Over 20 years experience in finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gary Plotzza</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/gary-plotzza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/gary-plotzza/</guid>
      <description> Over the last 16 years I ve worked as a mortgage and finance broker in Melbourne s south eastern suburbs. I m also a fully qualified Financial Planner. I m perfectly placed to give you important information and guidance on choosing your ideal home loan or finance product. Whether you re looking for a business
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gavin Frith</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/gavin-frith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/gavin-frith/</guid>
      <description> We help you find the right home loan and work with you
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gee Taggar</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/gee-taggar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/gee-taggar/</guid>
      <description> Residential/ Commercial/ Asset finance I am currently the director and founder of Archer Mortgage Group. I am a fully accredited mortgage broker and hold membership with the Mortgage and Finance Association of Australia (MFAA). Having worked exceptionally hard through more than 7 years in the finance industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geoff Blethyn</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/geoff-blethyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/geoff-blethyn/</guid>
      <description>I started in 2004 as the franchisee for Destiny Financial Solutions for 5 years During that time we helped clients purchase and finance investment property all over Australia with the appropriate cash flows and a 10 year plan. In 2008 we started In Good Company Australia and also opened a branch in Malaysia helping expats and migrants understand the property and finance issues here in Australia.In 2010 we were asked to give advice to high net worth clients of the EON bank with several seminars through Malaysia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Barakat</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/george-barakat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/george-barakat/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Kozah</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/george-kozah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/george-kozah/</guid>
      <description> A proven Mortgage Broker with 9 years experience in the Financial &amp;amp; Credit services industry. Coming from a Financial Planning background
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Mihalopoulos</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/george-mihalopoulos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/george-mihalopoulos/</guid>
      <description> Not all mortgage brokers are created equal! With over 19 years of extensive lending experience in both residential and commercial lending
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Smith</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/george-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/george-smith/</guid>
      <description> Being independently owned allows the flexibility to tailor our service to you. Your needs are paramount
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Zagas</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/george-zagas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/george-zagas/</guid>
      <description> Service commitment is second to none. Work with my clients to ensure they understand their options
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girish Ganglani</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/girish-ganglani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/girish-ganglani/</guid>
      <description> Friendly
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Rowan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/glenn-rowan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/glenn-rowan/</guid>
      <description> I have worked in various roles within the finance sector over the past 20 years. From Telling
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graeme Northcott</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/graeme-northcott/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/graeme-northcott/</guid>
      <description>  Experienced in Residential   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graham Lee</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/graham-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/graham-lee/</guid>
      <description> Commercial Finance &amp;amp; Leasing are accredited with over 40 financial institutions
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greg Clough</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/greg-clough/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/greg-clough/</guid>
      <description> With 15 years industry experience we have enjoyed guiding and assisting many hundreds of clients in a friendly and consultative style. I personally spend time with you to ensure every step of the process is thoroughly understood and stress-free. I look forward to working with you. Warm Regards Greg
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greg Mcguinness</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/greg-mcguinness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/greg-mcguinness/</guid>
      <description> I have over 12 years broking experience. I am focussed on saving clients money who have large loans and investment properties. Over the past 6 months I have saved clients between $1
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greg Nolan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/greg-nolan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/greg-nolan/</guid>
      <description> With all the different finance offerings available it is great to be able to help people sort out the best option for their needs. My experience with a major bank
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greg Sawyer</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/greg-sawyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/greg-sawyer/</guid>
      <description>I am a highly experienced mortgage broker that is passionate about finding my clients great value home loans that suit their needs from a large variety of lenders. *My firm can provide you with over 300 home loan options from 21 major lenders. *Our mortgage broking service is free of charge to our customers. *We take the hassle out of applying for a home loan and work hard to obtain fast home loan approvals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gregory Le Messurier</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/gregory-le-messurier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/gregory-le-messurier/</guid>
      <description> Over 20 years experience in the Financial services industry throughout Regional NSW
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guido Torelli</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/guido-torelli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/guido-torelli/</guid>
      <description> Whether you??re a first homebuyer
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hamish Riley</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/hamish-riley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/hamish-riley/</guid>
      <description> I have lived in Bendigo and Central Victoria my whole life
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hana Vano</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/hana-vano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/hana-vano/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hannah Abrahamson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/hannah-abrahamson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/hannah-abrahamson/</guid>
      <description> Whether you are purchasing a new property
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harnath Sithamraju</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/harnath-sithamraju/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/harnath-sithamraju/</guid>
      <description> I have over 33 years of working experience in Banks and Financial Services companies in India
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Kalaitsidis</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/harry-kalaitsidis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/harry-kalaitsidis/</guid>
      <description> At Cura Finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvinder Mann</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/harvinder-mann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/harvinder-mann/</guid>
      <description> Harvi has been with Sonic Finance Group since the start of the business in 2012. Prior to joining Sonic Finance Harvi worked at Nab Business Banking for five years dealing with business clients. Some of Harvi??s strengths are attention to detail
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hayden Dempsey</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/hayden-dempsey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/hayden-dempsey/</guid>
      <description> Hayden started his company Premium Portfolio Finance to continue and extend his passion for achieving long term financial goals with his clients. His experiences with mortgages range from first home buyers to complex company structures. Purchasing a new home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heena Shah</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/heena-shah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/heena-shah/</guid>
      <description>I am one of the Senior Finance Consultants at Amani Finance With 11 years of lending experience in most areas of Banking various Top Mobile Lender awards won over the years over which positive customer surveys have consistently been given I believe I have the credentials to look after the finance needs of my customers I generally find pleasure in helping people and I believe that success in any customer services role boils down to being a giver rather than a taker I am always prepared to go the extra mile to help people achieve their financial dreams and will without fail aim to look for outside of the square solution for my clients to help them to achieve their goals</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helena Hubena</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/helena-hubena/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/helena-hubena/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hema Gupta</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/hema-gupta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/hema-gupta/</guid>
      <description> I have been in the finance industry for over 9 years and have helped a lot of client to purchase their first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Zhang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/hunter-zhang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/hunter-zhang/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian Freeman</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ian-freeman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ian-freeman/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignatius Theodos</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ignatius-theodos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ignatius-theodos/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;ll let my clients speak on my behalf. Please check out our reviews under Aussie Mt Lawley on Facebook and Google. Here is a sample: Through a recommendation from a friend
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isabelle Ou</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/isabelle-ou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/isabelle-ou/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iva Rasic</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/iva-rasic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/iva-rasic/</guid>
      <description>As Senior Mortgage Broker for the BorrowRight team, I pride myself in going above and beyond for all our clients. Having worked in Financial Services for over 3 years, I have extensive knowledge of the lending process. In the meantime, I have earned a Commerce Degree (MJR in Marketing) from Macquarie University, completed my Certificate IV in Mortgage Broking and recently completed a Certificate in Real Estate Sales and Property Management from REINSW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivano Lino</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ivano-lino/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ivano-lino/</guid>
      <description> Creating strategies
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Tarchichi</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jack-tarchichi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jack-tarchichi/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Wei</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jack-wei/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jack-wei/</guid>
      <description> Our highly experienced team has over 19 years of combined experience in finance industry. During this time, weve helped many people significantly improve their financial independence and security. Get to know more about our team and how we can help you.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob Decru</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jacob-decru/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jacob-decru/</guid>
      <description> Whether you??re buying your first property
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacqueline Wang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jacqueline-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jacqueline-wang/</guid>
      <description> I am nominated by Mortgage Professionals Australia as one of the top Young Guns 2016. I am also nominated by The Adviser as Top 30 Young Broker of the Year 2016. As a broker i have access to a wide range of lenders
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jai Martinkovits</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jai-martinkovits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jai-martinkovits/</guid>
      <description> Jai is Managing Director of Finance Ferret. His clients enjoy a close ongoing professional relationship built on trust. Jai s clients also appreciate his ability to explain complex concepts in simple everyday language.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Belov</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/james-belov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/james-belov/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Cairncross</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/james-cairncross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/james-cairncross/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Millard</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/james-millard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/james-millard/</guid>
      <description> I believe that having the right loan structure is key to being able to focus on what&amp;rsquo;s important to you and live a worry-free life. Everyone should have access to the right lending to help them buy the home of their dreams or to build their investment portfolio. Being self employed
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Sim</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/james-sim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/james-sim/</guid>
      <description> As a qualified accountant
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Stavrou</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/james-stavrou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/james-stavrou/</guid>
      <description> I am a results-driven professional with years of experience in banking. Hardworking
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Sylvester</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/james-sylvester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/james-sylvester/</guid>
      <description> James Sylvester starting Mortgage Broking in 2009 and established Your Home Loan Consultant in 2012. Mortgage broking specialist and property investment consultant. We assist our clients to create wealth safely without compromising their lifestyle. General advice on all things finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Zhang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/james-zhang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/james-zhang/</guid>
      <description> Method Finance has an in-depth knowledge of the mortgage and financial industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jarrod Gillespie</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jarrod-gillespie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jarrod-gillespie/</guid>
      <description> I love building new relationships and helping people achieve their dreams! I will work with you to help you find the best deal that suits your current needs and stay in touch with you post settlement of your new loan to ensure any changes to your situation are met and understood. Call me today!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jas Khara</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jas-khara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jas-khara/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason He</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jason-he/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jason-he/</guid>
      <description> Hi there! Thanks for looking into my profile. I am the principal mortgage consultant at Jason He Financial in Parramatta. I have 8 years finance and banking experience across Westpac
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Prichard</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jason-prichard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jason-prichard/</guid>
      <description> We aim to provide clients with the edge in finding the best loan and rates for the individual situation. Other than finding the best loan
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Strazds</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jason-strazds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jason-strazds/</guid>
      <description> When it comes to organising finance there&amp;rsquo;s a couple of things most people want. A great rate without all the fuss. At Hassle Free Finance that is exactly what we deliver. A truely personalised service built around understanding your needs and vision. We work for you! I bring 15+ years of banking
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jassie Marok</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jassie-marok/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jassie-marok/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jay Gangoda</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jay-gangoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jay-gangoda/</guid>
      <description> 16 yrs experience as an MFAA Credit Adviser
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jay Jayasuriya</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jay-jayasuriya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jay-jayasuriya/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m committed to making every customer interaction a highly satisfying one.&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; Jay Jayasuriya is an experienced mortgage consultant with over 10 years&amp;rsquo; experience working in the banking and finance industry in Australia and United Kingdom. Jay has a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in business from the university of east London and a Diploma in mortgage brokering and financial planning. Jay is well regarded as someone who is committed to make every customer interaction a highly satisfying one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean-Jacques Fiasson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jean-jacques-fiasson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jean-jacques-fiasson/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Harris</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jeff-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jeff-harris/</guid>
      <description> Experienced Mortgage Broker with access to 35 different Lenders. This allows me to compare lenders and find you the best option. Specializing in: Home Loans
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Bachir</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jennifer-bachir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jennifer-bachir/</guid>
      <description> Jennifer Bachir
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Chambers</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jennifer-chambers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jennifer-chambers/</guid>
      <description> Pioneer Finance Solutions covers all aspects of finance broking (from home and investment loans
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Smith</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jennifer-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jennifer-smith/</guid>
      <description> As a real estate investor myself
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy Fisher</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jeremy-fisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jeremy-fisher/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Martino</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jerry-martino/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jerry-martino/</guid>
      <description>I am a broker with 20 years lending experience working with a team to ensure the best results for our clients. I m also a qualified Financial Adviser which enables me to assist clients with their financial needs. Our Company Mission is to build longevity with our customers and we do this by working in an ethical and trusted manner. Which coupled with our experience ensures that we are always adding value and exceeding customer expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jess Phillips</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jess-phillips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jess-phillips/</guid>
      <description> With a genuine caring and communicative approach
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessica Preston</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jessica-preston/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jessica-preston/</guid>
      <description> Jessica Preston is a member of the Chartered Institute of Management Accountants
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessie Wang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jessie-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jessie-wang/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Chen</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jimmy-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jimmy-chen/</guid>
      <description> I am an experienced and friendly mortgage broker and I know all aspects of property investment and business finance. I am good at home loans
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joanne Foltman</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/joanne-foltman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/joanne-foltman/</guid>
      <description> Joanne has a strong financial markets background having worked in the investment banking industry for over 14 years. With high attention to detail and a strong mind for numbers
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Bartilotta</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/joe-bartilotta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/joe-bartilotta/</guid>
      <description> Whether you are buying your first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Gardiner</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/joe-gardiner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/joe-gardiner/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Mennea</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/joe-mennea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/joe-mennea/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Palummo</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/joe-palummo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/joe-palummo/</guid>
      <description>I look at your needs as well as your long-term goals to ensure that I get you the best loan available. I will be there throughout the whole process from securing the approval from the bank to settlement guiding you each step on the way. I understand that everyone??s needs are different and every banks policies are different. I will navigate you to the banks that have the right products and service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel De Shannon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/joel-de-shannon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/joel-de-shannon/</guid>
      <description> AIIS was established in 2003 by its founder Joel De Shannon with a simple primary aim - To help our clients reduce debt and increase wealth through effective debt reduction strategies and market leading customer service. Contact our team today for your free Property Report and personalised debt reduction plan.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel Flanagan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/joel-flanagan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/joel-flanagan/</guid>
      <description> Joel is a home loan specialist providing a professional service for each and every client. He specialises in helping
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Adams</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/john-adams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/john-adams/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Hall</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/john-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/john-hall/</guid>
      <description> A professional Finance &amp;amp; Mortgage Adviser
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Kilgore</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/john-kilgore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/john-kilgore/</guid>
      <description>Originally from Scotland I have the traditional Scottish approach to matters of finance. What I like to do with clients is conduct full and due diligence on all matters concerning their finances. You will find my attention to detail is next to none. I have over 20 years experience in financial services industry both here in Australia and the UK. Much of that time was spent working with some of the world s largest investment banks including Citibank</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Kraws</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/john-kraws/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/john-kraws/</guid>
      <description> I have over 20 years experience in borrowing and investing in property
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Macalyk</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/john-macalyk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/john-macalyk/</guid>
      <description> If Experience counts
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Marchetta</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/john-marchetta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/john-marchetta/</guid>
      <description> Experienced finance professional with access to low rate deals from multiple lenders. I am committed to high levels of customer service and am available most evenings and weekends.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Pedler</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/john-pedler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/john-pedler/</guid>
      <description> I have more than 40 years finance industry experience. In our brokerage we can assist not only with housing finance but business
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Salamastrakis</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/john-salamastrakis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/john-salamastrakis/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t ever stop dreaming as dreams are the road to success. This is my motto and I help you achieve your Financial dreams. I have a passion and personal interest in real estate gives me the expertise to understand your property goals and your future financial achievements. I have a customer focus that is entrenched from years in the service industry. Developing and maintaining client relationships are my foremost priorities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Valentine</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/john-valentine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/john-valentine/</guid>
      <description> I have a professional background with over 15 years?? experience in the mortgage industry. Over the years
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Encavey</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jonathan-encavey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jonathan-encavey/</guid>
      <description> Jonathan has over 8 years experience in the banking and wealth management industries. While working with Deloitte and the Financial Ombudsman Service; Jonathan specialised in compliance and regulation of advice across the financial sector. He aided in the development of advice models that are still used today by financial institutions both in Australia and the UK.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonathon Coleman</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jonathon-coleman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jonathon-coleman/</guid>
      <description> Jonathon is the Managing Director of One Stone Finance. A 100% Tasmanian owned and operated company with a trusted reputation. With over 11 years experience in mortgage broking
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Choo</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jordan-choo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jordan-choo/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Papadopoulos</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jordan-papadopoulos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jordan-papadopoulos/</guid>
      <description> A close connection to the inner Northern suburbs and its surrounds comes from having grown up in the area and later together with my wife purchased our first home. We still live locally and have maintained an active involvement in the local community and sporting clubs. With over a decade of experience in the financial industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Vecchio</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/joshua-vecchio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/joshua-vecchio/</guid>
      <description> Are you after the best home and investment loan? With so many banks offering you loans and incentives it can all be overwhelming
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julie Rashleigh</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/julie-rashleigh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/julie-rashleigh/</guid>
      <description>I am an experienced mortgage broker having had over 20 years experience in finance and lending. I will ensure that I find the best possible loan to suit your immediate needs and future goals. I like to work with my clients to ensure that I fully understand their personal &amp;amp; financial situation in order to find the best possible solution for them. I am happy to meet with my clients wherever is suitable to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Ishac</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/justin-ishac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/justin-ishac/</guid>
      <description> I have extensive years of experience within the finance sector. At Auswide Credit and Finance we specialise in assisting our clients find the right loans specifically tailored to the needs of our clients.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Joyce</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/justin-joyce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/justin-joyce/</guid>
      <description> Your go to for any finance needs. Whether you are looking to purchase your first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kai Xu</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kai-xu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kai-xu/</guid>
      <description> Specialise in: residential
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalki French</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kalki-french/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kalki-french/</guid>
      <description> With a strong background of financial planning with a major group
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karen Emerson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/karen-emerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/karen-emerson/</guid>
      <description> Lending Options is a boutique finance broking firm that provides clients with professional guidance through all aspects of their financing. I recognise that each client has specific needs in relation to obtaining their finance. I strive to meet those unique requirements through my knowledge and expertise gained from over 25 years hands-on experience in the mortgage and finance industry. Lending Options is a one stop shop
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karen Fowles</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/karen-fowles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/karen-fowles/</guid>
      <description> I grew up on the Gold Coast &amp;amp; have extensive Finance Industry experience of more than 30 years both in Qld &amp;amp; interstate. I am passionate about helping my clients achieve their financial goals and providing them with best options to improve cash flow. I really endeavour to assist my clients every step of the way to ensure that their financial journey is stress free.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karl Bower</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/karl-bower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/karl-bower/</guid>
      <description> Bower &amp;amp; Co. are specialist advisors in lending
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kasra Sharifi</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kasra-sharifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kasra-sharifi/</guid>
      <description> I was drawn to the Finance Industry through his enjoyment of people
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kate Leunig</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kate-leunig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kate-leunig/</guid>
      <description>With over six years experience in the finance industry I have a strong understanding of all types of lending. With a background of broking in an accountancy firm I am as capable of dealing with complex lending scenarios as I am with a straight forward purchase or refinance. I will take my time to understand every client??s personal situation to ensure a smooth and stress free journey. My goal is to make sure all my clients?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathleen Mccormick</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kathleen-mccormick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kathleen-mccormick/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathy Robinson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kathy-robinson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kathy-robinson/</guid>
      <description> As an experienced Mortgage Broker I really enjoy helping people achieve their dreams by securing finance for whatever their needs may be. I lead from the front. I will work with you every step of the way to ensure a smooth and trouble free application process. Calling me will be the best move to make.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kc Johnson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kc-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kc-johnson/</guid>
      <description> Harlem Financial Group is a boutique brokerage firm servicing south east Queensland and beyond. We believe that the right loan starts with the right people and we take the guess work out of your transition into property ownership. With so much noise in the mortgage broking space our down to earth
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kelley Moss</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kelley-moss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kelley-moss/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kelvin Mason</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kelvin-mason/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kelvin-mason/</guid>
      <description> More Home ~ Less Loan : Residential
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ken Halliday</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ken-halliday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ken-halliday/</guid>
      <description> I ve been working as a mortgage broker for the past 6 years. I enjoy the role as I can make a big difference in peoples lives in different ways - helping them buy a home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ken Hew</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ken-hew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ken-hew/</guid>
      <description> As a Finance Broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Jin</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kevin-jin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kevin-jin/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Liu</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kevin-liu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kevin-liu/</guid>
      <description> As an experienced mortgage broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kirsten Nazzari</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kirsten-nazzari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kirsten-nazzari/</guid>
      <description> With over 10 years of experience in the finance industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kirsty Gardner</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kirsty-gardner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kirsty-gardner/</guid>
      <description> Whether you??re purchasing your first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kris Faife</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kris-faife/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kris-faife/</guid>
      <description> I??m an experienced finance broker and refinancing specialist
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kristian Orchard</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kristian-orchard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kristian-orchard/</guid>
      <description> Kristian Orchard has a proven track record as a reputable broker with an impressive background in the Finance and Real estate sector. Not only is he industry qualified his extensive knowledge of how the real estate industry operates makes him an informed finance/ property specialist. With a hands on approach
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kumar Thomas</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kumar-thomas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kumar-thomas/</guid>
      <description> Hello
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kurt Whittingham</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kurt-whittingham/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kurt-whittingham/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Scott</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kyle-scott/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kyle-scott/</guid>
      <description>Sherlock Homes Melbourne is your mortgage investigator. In todays world we are all time poor and the last thing we want to think about when we get home from work is finance. To take the pressure off you should let Sherlock do the hard work for you. We save our clients thousands of dollars and strip years off their home loans and helping clients to achieve their goals is what gets us out of bed every day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kym Russell</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kym-russell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kym-russell/</guid>
      <description> Kym joined the Nieuvision team in 2015 and has over 20 years experience in operations and senior financial management roles. His skills in identifying the issues and and developing the right longterm strategy has led to great results
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Lawa</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/laura-lawa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/laura-lawa/</guid>
      <description> My goal as a broker is to find you the best loan to suit your needs. I have a strong focus on education and ensure my clients are well informed leading to confident decisions. Buying property can be daunting
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurayne Walkerden</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/laurayne-walkerden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/laurayne-walkerden/</guid>
      <description> Mortgage Broker for more than 7 years
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lauren Eakins</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/lauren-eakins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/lauren-eakins/</guid>
      <description> Lauren has worked for all the major banks and knows how to tender your business to ensure you get competitive rates. We provide provide residential
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurence Adelman</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/laurence-adelman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/laurence-adelman/</guid>
      <description> I have been in Broking for 15 years. I am chartered accountant and an investment property holder. I can therefore assist with all kinds of loans. In fact I specialise in the difficult ones where the banks say no.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurence Kennedy</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/laurence-kennedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/laurence-kennedy/</guid>
      <description> With experience in loan structure I ensure that your needs are met and that the loan is set up correctly for your refinance or investment growth. We can look at how to pay your home loan off quicker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lawrence Meyer</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/lawrence-meyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/lawrence-meyer/</guid>
      <description>I have more than 20 years experience in Financial Services Products. (in South Africa and Australia). I am a Mortgage &amp;amp; Finance Association of Australia (MFAA) accredited Finance Broker and have completed the Diploma in Finance &amp;amp; Mortgage Broking Management. I am passionate in ensuring that my clients achieve their goals by providing them with a quality service which includes matching the most suitable Lender at the best rates that they qualify for</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leandro De Jesus</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/leandro-de-jesus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/leandro-de-jesus/</guid>
      <description> My genuine enthusiasm to help each and every one of my clients succeed with their property goals is clear in every instance. As an active property investor
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lee Wisniewski</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/lee-wisniewski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/lee-wisniewski/</guid>
      <description> Recognized at the Australian Mortgage Awards as a Finalist in the 2016 Quality Young Gun category! With over 13 years finance and insurance experience I have assisted more than 2000 people to get a loan and/or protect themselves against unforeseen life-changing events! Following emergency brain surgery in 2008 I discovered my purpose in life
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leo Cordedda</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/leo-cordedda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/leo-cordedda/</guid>
      <description> My priority is to ensure that his clients are happy with the loan structure and the service that I provide throughout the process and beyond. I have over 8 years?? experience as a Mortgage Broker and over 20 years experience in property investment. I am happy to cater for all clients and from First Home Owners
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lester Buch</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/lester-buch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/lester-buch/</guid>
      <description> I am a finance professional that offers out the square solutions. Whether you are looking to purchase your first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lester Li</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/lester-li/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/lester-li/</guid>
      <description> I am sophisticated and specialising in comparing different loan products to pursuit of successful settlement and achieve your goals. *First Home Buyers Solutions and Low Deposit Loans *Self Employed or Small Business Lending *Refinance or New Purchase Lending either in Residential or Commercial *Bad Credit Loans *Australia Expat Home Loans (Restricted Borrowers Types)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lezli Hyde</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/lezli-hyde/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/lezli-hyde/</guid>
      <description>My name is Lezli Hyde and I have a Diploma of Mortgage &amp;amp; Financial Management. Although I&amp;rsquo;m based in Melbourne - I do assist ANY borrower anywhere in Australia I will help any borrower - especially those who the Banks or even other Brokers won&amp;rsquo;t waste time helping. I have experience in procuring home loans for all types of borrowers - - Self Employed with ABN - Lo Doc Loans - First Home Owners - Credit Impaired - with UNPAID Defaults &amp;amp; Judgements - Part IX - Current Bankrupts - Refinance at a lower rate - Interest Only loans I will work very hard to help my borrowers obtain finance for whatever they wish to buy - a First</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linda D&#39;Vaz</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/linda-dvaz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/linda-dvaz/</guid>
      <description> I bring over 20 years of experience in various management
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lindsay Warner</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/lindsay-warner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/lindsay-warner/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about helping people achieve their property ownership goals! Whether it&amp;rsquo;s the first property purchase
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Donoghue</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/lisa-donoghue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/lisa-donoghue/</guid>
      <description> A hands on broker who believes in
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louis Teoh</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/louis-teoh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/louis-teoh/</guid>
      <description> Coming from profound corporate banking background and being a mortgage consultant now I have a grasp of what it takes to deliver a professional yet personal service to my clients. Every decision I make creates value for and is always in the best interests of my clients. To some people
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucas Seow</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/lucas-seow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/lucas-seow/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maggie Wan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/maggie-wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/maggie-wan/</guid>
      <description>I have worked in The Accounting and Finance Industry for a number of years. I am Passionate about helping clients find the best home loan for their individual needs. To me it is important to create a strategy for each and every client to not only get a fantastic home loan but pay it off as soon as possible. I am happy to help with all your home loan needs and walk you through every step of the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahesh Arora</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mahesh-arora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mahesh-arora/</guid>
      <description> Qualified Mortgage Broker Qualified Chartered Accountant Sydney cbd and Bella Vista Flame broker with St George Bank
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maninder Singh</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/maninder-singh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/maninder-singh/</guid>
      <description> Trusted mortgage broker providing services to clients. We make sure you get the right home loan for your circumstances and will manage the process from start to finish. Whether you re in the market for your first home or building a portfolio of investment properties
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marco Meloni</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/marco-meloni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/marco-meloni/</guid>
      <description> Hi
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marco Scannone</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/marco-scannone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/marco-scannone/</guid>
      <description> Thanks to my experience
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Margaret Spaseski</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/margaret-spaseski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/margaret-spaseski/</guid>
      <description> With over nineteen years of Banking &amp;amp; Finance experience and a passion for Property Investment within the Finance Industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maria Mejia</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/maria-mejia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/maria-mejia/</guid>
      <description> Having worked in banking and finance for over 10 years
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Camerlengo</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mario-camerlengo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mario-camerlengo/</guid>
      <description> Mario is a highly qualified and respected finance professional
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marios Rokka</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/marios-rokka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/marios-rokka/</guid>
      <description> EXPERIENCE: With over 17 years of experience in the industry I run a highly successful Mortgage Business with dedicated support staff and brokers who specialize in their field of knowledge so you know that you are always in good hands. AWARDS: Having been recognized with awards for Excellence in Customer Service and Excellence in Finance Brokering
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Davies</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mark-davies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mark-davies/</guid>
      <description> I ve worked in financial management for over 15 years
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Devenny</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mark-devenny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mark-devenny/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Hardy</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mark-hardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mark-hardy/</guid>
      <description>With 9+ years of Finance Industry experience I bring a range of knowledge and experience to the table. My understanding of &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;Bank Talk&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; allows me to ensure my clients completely understand every aspect of their loan. Every client wants (and deserves) the best finance deal to meet their borrowing needs. That&amp;rsquo;s where I come in!!!!! I&amp;rsquo;m an experienced broker and have great relationships with Australia&amp;rsquo;s leading lenders and banks which provides access to competitive finance deals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Harrison</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mark-harrison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mark-harrison/</guid>
      <description> &amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo;I specialise in providing the most suitable product to meet your expectations and requirements. This may be to purchase the home of your dreams or simply structure the finance to your needs.&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; My name??s Mark Harrison and I??ve been working in the finance sector for over 25 years. While I live in the Tweed Heads area
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Monahan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mark-monahan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mark-monahan/</guid>
      <description> I have worked with Eastern Financial Solutions as a Mortgage Broker since 2012. Eastern Financial Solutions are affiliated with over 25 lenders and our aim is to assist our clients make an informed decision about the most appropriate product and lender to suit their needs. My previous experience includes over 6 years lending and banking experience working for Westpac Banking Corporation in a variety of roles.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Wong</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mark-wong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mark-wong/</guid>
      <description> Hello
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martin Ferreira</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/martin-ferreira/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/martin-ferreira/</guid>
      <description> Commercially and financially experienced
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martin Mureithi</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/martin-mureithi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/martin-mureithi/</guid>
      <description>The decision to buy a property and taking out a mortgage is one of the most significant decisions a person gets to make in their lifetime. It can be a daunting and very stressful experience especially when you haven&amp;rsquo;t got somebody holding your hand and pointing you in the right direction. I am here to make that process as manageable and stress free as I can for you. I enjoy working with people and always strive to deliver the best possible experience and outcomes for my customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martin Zachara</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/martin-zachara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/martin-zachara/</guid>
      <description> Achieving more than 15 years in Banking and Finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marty Oke</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/marty-oke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/marty-oke/</guid>
      <description> At Ultimate Finance Group we have a team of 3 brokers who are determined to help our customers find the best deal for their home loan. We can help with all aspects of lending from refinancing to save money
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martyn Williams</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/martyn-williams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/martyn-williams/</guid>
      <description> Thank you for taking the time to read my profile. My role is to make your experience of buying or refinancing as pleasurable as possible
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mary Abbey</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mary-abbey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mary-abbey/</guid>
      <description>Abbey Financial Services is a team run by Mary Abbey. Mary has many years experience in the finance industry in residential and commercial finance with an office in Canberra and Melbourne. We pride ourselves on our ability to laterally assess a situation and give you the best direction for your future financial and personal goals with the utmost communication and support available. We look foward to speaking with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mas Pourgholami</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mas-pourgholami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mas-pourgholami/</guid>
      <description> Whether you are purchasing a new property
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathew Ness</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mathew-ness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mathew-ness/</guid>
      <description> An experienced Mortgage Broker who believes in finding a solution for a client that is unique to them and their specific life circumstances and events. &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;Loans are not a one size fits all&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; scenario. I like to tailor a loan that allows for an improved financial position balanced with a positive lifestyle influence.&amp;rdquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathew Spiteri</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mathew-spiteri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mathew-spiteri/</guid>
      <description> Beyond finding the finance solution that best suits your scenario
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Dornbusch</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/matt-dornbusch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/matt-dornbusch/</guid>
      <description> Matt has an extensive background in corporate banking and finance spending 15 years in a variety of senior finance roles with the major banks. Matt holds a Bachelor of Business
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Haines</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/matt-haines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/matt-haines/</guid>
      <description> At Optimum home Loans and Finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Hall</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/matt-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/matt-hall/</guid>
      <description> Greetings and Salutations
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Hayes</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-hayes/</guid>
      <description> Matthew grew up in Canberra
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Lefroy</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-lefroy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-lefroy/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Reece</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-reece/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-reece/</guid>
      <description> I am a Senior Mortgage Broker at Loanseeker Home Loans. I am a former accountant and have worked in finance for over 10 years. I have excellent product knowledge of the 40+ residential lenders that I represent and I&amp;rsquo;m sure I can help you structure your finances to get the best long term results.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Robins</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-robins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-robins/</guid>
      <description> Sadly
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Stammers</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-stammers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-stammers/</guid>
      <description> Matt is a key part of the family business that is Smartline Mortgage Brokers Applecross. He has worked for a number of years alongside his father Paul Stammers
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Woods</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-woods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/matthew-woods/</guid>
      <description> With more than sixteen years experience working for some of the country??s biggest banks
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maurizio Barba</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/maurizio-barba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/maurizio-barba/</guid>
      <description> With so many options out there finding the right home loan can be challenging. Having the right broker who can help you with this is important. I&amp;rsquo;ve helped my clients not only get into the right home loan but also make sure they are structured properly to achieve future goals.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max Harris</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/max-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/max-harris/</guid>
      <description> Born and raised in the eastern suburbs of Sydney
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mayank Pankhania</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mayank-pankhania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mayank-pankhania/</guid>
      <description> Our name hints at our Values and what we identify with both as an organisation and as individuals. Our slogan: ENRICH YOUR WORLD encompasses our passion to make a difference by running a Business for Good . We run a business focused on CONTRIBUTION rather than the traditional business that is focused on Consumption. We aim to achieve this through Knowledge
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaghen Di Santo</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/meaghen-di-santo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/meaghen-di-santo/</guid>
      <description> As a Mortgage Broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melanie Burns</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/melanie-burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/melanie-burns/</guid>
      <description> Sherlock Holmes Lending Solutions emerged primarily to help fill a void in the mortgage and finance landscape. A void where rates are not all they&amp;rsquo;re cracked up to be
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melinda Mahon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/melinda-mahon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/melinda-mahon/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melinda Nash</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/melinda-nash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/melinda-nash/</guid>
      <description>Hello! You will enjoy working with me as I help you to secure the most appropriate loan product for you. I am tenacious in getting great outcomes for my clients. The process will be easy and smooth for you and I will keep you posted every step of the way. Please refer to my website to see testimonials from happy customers at www.integrilend.com.au and connect with my business page on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melissa Cavers</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/melissa-cavers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/melissa-cavers/</guid>
      <description> Your Mortgage and Finance advice is in good hands with Melissa
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cullinan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-cullinan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-cullinan/</guid>
      <description> Rapid Finance offers innovative
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Finn</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-finn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-finn/</guid>
      <description> If you need a mortgage broker in the northern Gold Coast area Michael Finn is ready to help you find the best loan from over 40 lenders to suit your property finance needs. Michael has 16 years of experience as a mortgage broker and is also a licensed financial planner. He??s passionate about helping people achieve their financial dreams
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Garland</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-garland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-garland/</guid>
      <description> Home Loan Specialist for First Home Buyers. A genuine and honest broker committed to helping individuals and couples successfully complete their first home purchase. The more complex and difficult your needs are
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Hamilton</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-hamilton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-hamilton/</guid>
      <description> In partnership with HashChing&amp;rsquo;s #1 rated broker Lee Wisniewski
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jin</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-jin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-jin/</guid>
      <description> I have 6 years of experience in the finance and broking industry. Currently I am a senior manager at N1 Loans Pty Ltd
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Kiang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-kiang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-kiang/</guid>
      <description> Choosing a loan is easy&amp;hellip; Choosing a mortgage broker to help you find that loan is hard. What makes us more qualified to assist you: 1. over 10years experience in home loan advice. Combined with bachelor of finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Kimbel</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-kimbel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-kimbel/</guid>
      <description>With over 10 years of finance experience I have assisted many clients with sourcing and securing suitable lending options to ensure the best financial structures have been established. My strength is looking at the client??s overall financial situation and structuring a lending platform that best suits their requirements. I have a passion for property investing and I share that passion with my clients. Many clients have been able to establish a significant property portfolio thanks to the lending structure that I have established for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Mckenzie</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-mckenzie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-mckenzie/</guid>
      <description> Finance broker and property investor/ developer for over 15 years. Still passionate about helping others get into their dream homes and create wealth.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Messinesi</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-messinesi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-messinesi/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Parsons</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-parsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-parsons/</guid>
      <description> I am creative
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Pascarelli</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-pascarelli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-pascarelli/</guid>
      <description> I am a Senior Finance Manager for the fastest growing mortgage brokerage company in Australia . Whatever you are looking for
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Paulse</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-paulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-paulse/</guid>
      <description> Xskape Finance is well established Mortgage Broking business. We aim to source and deliver finance solutions tailored to our customers needs. As the principal of Xskape Finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Short</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-short/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-short/</guid>
      <description>I am an experienced financial adviser and mortgage broker with a track record of helping clients find the optimal and most efficient solutions to their financial needs. This includes helping with structuring and finding the right home loan as well as most other aspects of personal finance. I can help with: Residential Loans Investment Loans Land and Construction Loans SMSF Lending Commercial Lending They say that it takes a mortgage broker to get you in to debt and a financial adviser to help you get out debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Sion</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michael-sion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michael-sion/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;m a very hands on broker making sure every client is treated with respect and attention. My mantra is to find a loan for each client as hard as I would try for myself. I have strong relationships with a number of banks to assist you in your financial pursuits.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Dexter</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-dexter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-dexter/</guid>
      <description> Having worked in banking
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Hudson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-hudson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-hudson/</guid>
      <description> I had been working in the banking and finance industry for many years . I decided to become a Finance Broker as I wanted to be able to offer my clients a wider range of options with your best interest at heart. Everyone has different circumstances and needs. Whether you are a First Home Buyer that needs their hand held
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Ivanov</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-ivanov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-ivanov/</guid>
      <description> Hi everyone
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Milsom-Wright</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-milsom-wright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-milsom-wright/</guid>
      <description> The role of the Finance/Mortgage Broker is to source a borrowing facility that suits your business needs. This service saves you both valuable time and effort. By using Lend wRight Brokerage as Finance Brokers/Mortgage Brokers you can be assured you are being offered the best fit loan from a large range of different lenders. By being accredited with most leading Home Loan Lenders in Australia - major banks
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Murphy</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-murphy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/michelle-murphy/</guid>
      <description>Michelle Murphy has over 23 years of experience in the mortgage and insurance industry and is mortgage specialist throughout Australia. Michelle is perfectly placed to give you all the information you need to understand home loan market and different type of loans available. Michelle has made a career out of turning a challenging property experience into a truly rewarding experience for her clients. Michelle takes the time to explain the purchasing and mortgage process and take out the jargon to make it easier to navigate through process of purchasing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mikal Howard</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mikal-howard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mikal-howard/</guid>
      <description> As a passionate property investor I am able to bring personal experience to my role in the finance industry as a Mortgage Broker. To further boost my skills and knowledge
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mirella Cavallaro</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mirella-cavallaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mirella-cavallaro/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitch Tilbrook</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/mitch-tilbrook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/mitch-tilbrook/</guid>
      <description>My name is Mitch Tilbrook from Reality Home Loans. I&amp;rsquo;m in the business of helping Aussies make the Great Australian Dream a Reality. I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this for 6 years now and there&amp;rsquo;s not a lending situation I haven&amp;rsquo;t tackled. I have a customer service background and I love taking people on the winding road that is the property purchase experience and ensure you arrive safe and sound. My lender policy knowledge is exceptional so let me find you the lender most suited to your needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morris Bahbah</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/morris-bahbah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/morris-bahbah/</guid>
      <description> Unlimited Home Loans &amp;amp; Finance has made the dream of home ownership a reality for thousands of Australians by always seeking for the right deal for them. As part of the unlimited team I can search through hundreds of loans from Australia??s leading lenders
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murray Davies</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/murray-davies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/murray-davies/</guid>
      <description> providing professional advice and solutions 29 years experience
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nadia Davison</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nadia-davison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nadia-davison/</guid>
      <description> I love numbers and problem solving
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nalin De Silva</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nalin-de-silva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nalin-de-silva/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natasha Barber</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/natasha-barber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/natasha-barber/</guid>
      <description> I am one of the Senior Finance Consultants at Amani Finance. With 15 years of lending experience in most areas of Banking
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natasha Bianchini</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/natasha-bianchini/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/natasha-bianchini/</guid>
      <description> With over 10 years of experience in the finance industry I have come across just about every loan scenario possible. I am supremely confident that if I can??t find you a loan then no one can! I maintain a thorough approach in assessing my clients financial situations. I specialise in tailor made finance solutions that will ensure you pay your loans off as fast as you possibly can
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Brand</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nathan-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nathan-brand/</guid>
      <description> Hi
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Osinski</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nathan-osinski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nathan-osinski/</guid>
      <description> In today&amp;rsquo;s market you can obtain a mortgage from a variety of lenders. However
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Sitas</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nathan-sitas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nathan-sitas/</guid>
      <description> My aim is to help me clients achieve their goals through finance. This includes those looking to buy a home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Vecchio</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nathan-vecchio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nathan-vecchio/</guid>
      <description>At Hunter Galloway - Home Loan Experts we are absolutely committed to our customer through a high level of service and advice. With over 30 specialised lenders offering more than 300 loan solutions: * Our service is at no cost to you * We assist customers Australia wide * Keep the process easy and hassle free * Gain loan approval as soon as possible * Offer RP Data reports at no cost to our customers * Ability to arrange free valuations and credit reports * Take a holistic approach * With an exceptional reputation Hunter Galloway - Home Loan Experts provides a personalised approach to mortgage brokering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nayesh Shah</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nayesh-shah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nayesh-shah/</guid>
      <description>I am an experienced and capable mortgage broker with formal qualifications in Accounting and Finance. I completed my Masters from University of Sydney in 2005 and ever since then have been working in Finance Industry. Being a fully licensed broker through the Mortgage and Finance Association of Australia (MFAA) I ensure I work to the highest professional standards and provide quality advice to my clients. With access to over 30 different lenders I help my clients to get the right deal not the cheapest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neil Kumar</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/neil-kumar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/neil-kumar/</guid>
      <description> I am a professional Finance Broker and member of the UNIQ Group. As a Lending Advisor
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nerses Emilian</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nerses-emilian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nerses-emilian/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicholas Bateup</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nicholas-bateup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nicholas-bateup/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicholas Kirlew</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nicholas-kirlew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nicholas-kirlew/</guid>
      <description> Mortgage Brokers to Darwin and the Northern Territory. More than just a mortgage broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicholas Pantu</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nicholas-pantu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nicholas-pantu/</guid>
      <description> Nick is a Principal and Representative of Prime Time Advisory
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick Athanasiadis</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nick-athanasiadis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nick-athanasiadis/</guid>
      <description> Based on extensive professional qualifications and intimate industry knowledge
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick Aves</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nick-aves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nick-aves/</guid>
      <description> Nick??s devotion to his work has seen him receive PLAN Australia??s Sales Master Award every year since its establishment in 2005. He was also recognised in the MPA top 100 brokers of Australia in 2007. With a Diploma in Financial Services and a proven track record in the banking and finance industry as well as private business
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick Nasrallah</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nick-nasrallah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nick-nasrallah/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick Noble</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nick-noble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nick-noble/</guid>
      <description> I ve been a mortgage consultant for over 14 years and have assisted customers from first home buyers to investors. I m always happy to push the lenders for that bit extra for my clients.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicole	Cannon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nicolecannon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nicolecannon/</guid>
      <description> Pink Finance is Australia&amp;rsquo;s most recognised Broker for Ethics, Social Responsibility &amp;amp; Community Engagement. Nicole has been in the industry for 15 years and has a team dedicated to help you achieve your dreams.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicole Kennedy</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nicole-kennedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nicole-kennedy/</guid>
      <description> Specializing in Home Loans
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikhil Makati</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nikhil-makati/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nikhil-makati/</guid>
      <description>I have been working in the Finance &amp;amp; Mortgage Broking Industry since 2009. My broad financial background (Masters in Finance &amp;amp; Fin. Planning; Dip. in M &amp;amp; FM) and experience within the mortgage industry has helped me develop a personalised solution based approach to suit your situation and circumstances. We have access to over 30 lenders and over 300 different products to assist a range of mortgage options for you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Lewis</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nikki-lewis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nikki-lewis/</guid>
      <description> Nikki&amp;rsquo;s extensive experience and knowledge with 15 years in the finance industry will give you the opportunity to obtain the right home loan for your needs and will assist you every step of the way. Nikki has developed a personalised specialist service for brokered finance. With a passion for property Nikki loves helping her clients achieve their dreams of owning their first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Meldrum</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nikki-meldrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nikki-meldrum/</guid>
      <description> Nikki Meldrum established The Home Loan Professionals in Qld in 1997 Every transaction or discussion is done in strict confidence and at your most convenient time and place
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nolan Parodi</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nolan-parodi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nolan-parodi/</guid>
      <description> Hi
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oktay Sengoz</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/oktay-sengoz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/oktay-sengoz/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oliver Lum</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/oliver-lum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/oliver-lum/</guid>
      <description> Understanding your needs is paramount to finding the right fit for your lending needs. I take this approach with each and every one of my clients. The best deal is always always important
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oscar Chen</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/oscar-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/oscar-chen/</guid>
      <description> Customer service! Customer service! Customer Service! I do the comparison for you out of hundreds of products out of 30+ lenders. I offer extend business hours to suit your need. I am a Home loan
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Osman Duman</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/osman-duman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/osman-duman/</guid>
      <description> Based at Braeside
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pamela Palmqvist</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/pamela-palmqvist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/pamela-palmqvist/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pat Sciarrone</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/pat-sciarrone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/pat-sciarrone/</guid>
      <description>In 2008 PK INVEST was created to offer a full range of financial products and services to help all Australians build and manage their finances. PK INVEST??S Equity Accelerator Program is designed to reduce non-deductible debt. By consolidate your debt and restructure the way you manage your finances. Also included is mortgage monitoring and ongoing 6 monthly face to face review of your financial situation. With the main focus to reduce many years from your original loan term</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Kazzi</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/patrick-kazzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/patrick-kazzi/</guid>
      <description>Patrick has been associated with the Mortgage industry since 2003. During this time he has grown to understand the need to consider each client??s individual circumstances as part of tailoring a financial solution for them. His professional relationships and networks are one of the keys to his success as he has built strong relationships with a wide range of industry partners. Patrick is focused on providing his clients with sound advice and acting in their best interests to help them achieve the best possible outcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Morgan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/patrick-morgan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/patrick-morgan/</guid>
      <description> 2017 Finsure Young Gun of the Year finalist. Based in Melbourne
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Avinante</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/paul-avinante/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/paul-avinante/</guid>
      <description> A licensed Finance Broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Campbell</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/paul-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/paul-campbell/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Dubois</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/paul-dubois/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/paul-dubois/</guid>
      <description> I have been involved in the Banking industry for 20 years working with the major banks and have been running my own mortgage broking business for the past 5 years.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Narline</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/paul-narline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/paul-narline/</guid>
      <description> I am an mortgage broker with years of experience
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Rozario</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/paul-rozario/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/paul-rozario/</guid>
      <description> With over 10 years?? experience in lending through the banking industry and as a qualified finance broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Zada</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/paul-zada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/paul-zada/</guid>
      <description> Paul has over a decade&amp;rsquo;s experience as a professional adviser with formal qualifications as a finance broker/credit adviser and chartered accountant. Paul is passionate about helping employees
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Desbrowe-Annear</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/peter-desbrowe-annear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/peter-desbrowe-annear/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Georgas</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/peter-georgas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/peter-georgas/</guid>
      <description> Based on extensive professional qualifications and intimate industry knowledge
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Kitchingman</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/peter-kitchingman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/peter-kitchingman/</guid>
      <description> I have been involved in the Finance Industry for almost 20 years. I have held various roles in lending credit
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Koutsouradis</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/peter-koutsouradis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/peter-koutsouradis/</guid>
      <description>IMPRESS Financial Solutions is a boutique mortgage brokering firm set up to challenge Australian Banks to get a better deal for all. We deal with over 35+ banks and have access to over 500 products so we can source and structure the best home loans for our customers. IMPRESS Financial Solutions is a high energy business entirely focused on the customer and the customer experience. IMPRESS Financial Solutions is different from other mortgage broking businesses because we focus on getting the consumer to engage with our brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Paily</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/peter-paily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/peter-paily/</guid>
      <description> I offer professional financial solutions to my clients to help them achieve their goals. It can be buying a home or investment property
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Thompson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/peter-thompson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/peter-thompson/</guid>
      <description> A former banker with in excess 30 years in finance and business. I am well &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;travelled&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; and will help you negotiate the myriad of loan options available to find an appropriate product that is not unsuitable for your needs.&amp;rdquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phil Carr</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/phil-carr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/phil-carr/</guid>
      <description> With over over 16 years of experience in the finance industry I strive to achieve not only the best rate for a client but also the best customer experience. Prior to joining the MC Mortgage Solutions
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phil Lau</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/phil-lau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/phil-lau/</guid>
      <description>Phil Lau is a proven financial service professional with a passion for helping his clients achieve their financial goals. Phil began his career as a Chartered Accountant and has over 20 years of experience in accounting and finance for major international and national professional advisory firms. Our approach is a value added holistic model where we value and promote the experience and capability of the individuals seeking finance. We create a business case and provide a structured approach to the funding opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phillip Verheijen</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/phillip-verheijen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/phillip-verheijen/</guid>
      <description> I love helping people to achieve their hopes and dreams. With 15 years experience in Home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pola Perry</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/pola-perry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/pola-perry/</guid>
      <description> As director and broker at Advance Mobile Lending (Taylors Lakes
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prabuddha Malekoo</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/prabuddha-malekoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/prabuddha-malekoo/</guid>
      <description> With more than 12 years of experience in the banking and finance industry worked at a major Australian bank as a home lending manager
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pragash Santi</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/pragash-santi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/pragash-santi/</guid>
      <description> Working in the financial services industry with both small and large banks for more than 17 years gives me good understanding of banks credit policy
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prashneel Karan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/prashneel-karan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/prashneel-karan/</guid>
      <description> I am a Financial Planner and Mortgage Broker with Tranquillity Wealth. I work with clients to enhance their wealth journey. I work best with clients who are willing to take advice and are ready to commit to getting the most out of their life. I can assist clients on their wealth management journey as well as assist them in purchasing their next property
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queenie Kwong</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/queenie-kwong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/queenie-kwong/</guid>
      <description> Enthusiastic
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rachael Hunter</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/rachael-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/rachael-hunter/</guid>
      <description> Having lived in the Canberra area for over 20 years and being a home owner myself
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raj Achariya</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/raj-achariya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/raj-achariya/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramune Dimovska</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ramune-dimovska/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ramune-dimovska/</guid>
      <description> Dynamic Mortgage Broker helping busy people find the best loan that suits your needs and not the banks. My goal is to make it easy for you
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Randa Boutros</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/randa-boutros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/randa-boutros/</guid>
      <description> Her core product is offering property finance to all buyers with differing scenarios - home and commercial. A passion for real estate and property investment consulting has led Randa to establish a business that offers unique services in these areas. A keen eye for real estate strategies that suit different buyers
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Randy Bishop</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/randy-bishop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/randy-bishop/</guid>
      <description> Working for Sami L Home Loans with a Diploma of Finance &amp;amp; Mortgage Broking plus a Bachelor of Business (Accounting). I come with not only a wealth of qualifications but also plenty of on the job knowledge
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebecca Little</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/rebecca-little/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/rebecca-little/</guid>
      <description> I love what I do! There is nothing more exciting than helping people
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reet Gill</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/reet-gill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/reet-gill/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renato Cantalupo</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/renato-cantalupo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/renato-cantalupo/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Boalch</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/richard-boalch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/richard-boalch/</guid>
      <description> Richard has enjoyed working in banking and finance since 1989. He brings to the table a wealth of experience gained from previous roles in Lending
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Recordon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/richard-recordon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/richard-recordon/</guid>
      <description> Industry professional with 9 years experience. Offering a unique money management tool to help you reduce debt and become financially free sooner. Imagine paying your mortgage of in 15 years not 30.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Windeyer</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/richard-windeyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/richard-windeyer/</guid>
      <description> Leverage my experience. I deliver strategic home and investment loan advice with a first class experience
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Prabhakar</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/rishi-prabhakar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/rishi-prabhakar/</guid>
      <description> My name is Rishi Prabhakar
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rob Emmett</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/rob-emmett/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/rob-emmett/</guid>
      <description> With over 25 years in the mortgage industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Elton</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/robert-elton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/robert-elton/</guid>
      <description> Assisting Clients in their Financial needs for over 17 years Our Australian Credit Licence and tailored systems are your Sleep Easy Guarantee Our Loan Analytics cut through the confusion empowering you to move forward confidently I compare 100s of loans
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Gilto</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/robert-gilto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/robert-gilto/</guid>
      <description> I work to get my client home loan approval in a timely manner. I work with all the top lenders to find a suitable product for you.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Hartley</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/robert-hartley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/robert-hartley/</guid>
      <description> What I love most about my job is helping people realise their dreams
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Mcdougall</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/robert-mcdougall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/robert-mcdougall/</guid>
      <description> I know Townsville
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Mucci</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/robert-mucci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/robert-mucci/</guid>
      <description> Based in Richmond
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robin Webcke</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/robin-webcke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/robin-webcke/</guid>
      <description> I love my job. Greatest buzz from assisting clients achieve their dreams. Willing to travel anywhere either physically or electronically to meet new people. I am available seven days a week up to 9.30pm. Extensive experience in residential and investment lending. Specialise in SMSF lending and assisting with setting up Trusts at a very cheap rate. Car loans and personal lending OK.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocky Hoffman</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/rocky-hoffman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/rocky-hoffman/</guid>
      <description> I am motivated to assist individuals with all aspects of their finances and engage in discussions that would further enhance peoples understanding of finance and money
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocky Warren</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/rocky-warren/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/rocky-warren/</guid>
      <description> Operating since 2000 The Sydney Home Loan Centre is best known for its Boxing TV Commercials where it took on the Big Banks - in the ring - to get its clients a better deal. Specialising in Self Managed Super Funds including - Set Up
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rohan Puvi</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/rohan-puvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/rohan-puvi/</guid>
      <description> We are Prime Emerald Financial Services
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ron Lacoste</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ron-lacoste/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ron-lacoste/</guid>
      <description> I am the Managing Director with more than 20 years experience in the financial services industry with AMP. I am a fully accredited mortgage consultant with a Certificate IV in Finance &amp;amp; Mortgage Broking and a Diploma in Financial Planning.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ronald Stepnell</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ronald-stepnell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ronald-stepnell/</guid>
      <description> Our focus is on you- the client ! The Home Loan Advisory Service has been operating for over 20 years and with that comes the expertise to ensure the right result for your application. We will then be with there to provide the on-going service you need for the long term.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rory Mccann</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/rory-mccann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/rory-mccann/</guid>
      <description> Based in Sydney. A master negotiator
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ross Lovelock</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ross-lovelock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ross-lovelock/</guid>
      <description> Ross started his career
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russell Briggs</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/russell-briggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/russell-briggs/</guid>
      <description> You will always be the number 1 focus of my attention and I will always have your best interests at heart. A fully accredited mortgage broker in South West WA
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Miller</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ryan-miller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ryan-miller/</guid>
      <description> In a changing market
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan O&#39;Connor</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/ryan-oconnor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/ryan-oconnor/</guid>
      <description> With 16 years?? experience building strong
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sally Pietersz</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sally-pietersz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sally-pietersz/</guid>
      <description> I am a CPA Accountant
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sally Prowse</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sally-prowse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sally-prowse/</guid>
      <description> Sandcastle Finance has been helping people obtain the most appropriate finance for over a decade we are most passionate about showing clients how they can use other peoples money to grow a property portfolio that will ultimately give them a passive income for life
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam Chuang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sam-chuang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sam-chuang/</guid>
      <description>About Sam is an experienced home loan lender with over 10 years working at both local and international banks. Sam is a self taught front end-web developer and UI/UX designer. He responsibled for the operation and the development of Loans101 platform.
If you have any questions or feedback on how to make Loans101 a better place for customers and mortgage brokers, feel free to get in touch with Sam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam Lucci</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sam-lucci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sam-lucci/</guid>
      <description>With over 6 years experience in the finance industry &amp;amp; over 15 years experience in the corporate world holding various roles within the Sales &amp;amp; Marketing segment. I understand high excellence customer service. This is what I pride myself for as keeping the client in touch throughout the loan process &amp;amp; making sure that I am only a phone call away to answer any questions. I believe in giving my clients choice with loan products &amp;amp; finding a suitable product for that individual client need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandeep Mutti</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sandeep-mutti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sandeep-mutti/</guid>
      <description> Are you looking to purchase
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandy Padilla</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sandy-padilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sandy-padilla/</guid>
      <description> Happy Clients
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanjay Mario</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sanjay-mario/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sanjay-mario/</guid>
      <description> I have over 7 years experience in the finance and mortgage industry. Having worked at a major bank before
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanjiv Ahuja</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sanjiv-ahuja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sanjiv-ahuja/</guid>
      <description> Sanjiv has an extensive background in corporate and finance spending 15 years in a variety of senior finance roles within different industries. Sanjiv is a professionally qualified CA and CPA and is fully accredited with the Mortgage and Finance Association of Australia [MFAA] as a credit adviser
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santino Karras</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/santino-karras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/santino-karras/</guid>
      <description>Santino is the senior mortgage specialist at FreedomPath Financial a boutique mortgage broking business built on strong Customer Relationships. Santino will look after your debt needs and provide you with a Private Banking experience being your 1st point of contact at all times. Santino is personable and approachable. His experience and ability to understand your needs ensures you will always receive structured tailored advice and receive above and beyond market expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Goh</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sarah-goh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sarah-goh/</guid>
      <description> I am also a Certified Public Accountant and pro-active property investor with a passion to help people realise their Australian home owner??s dream. It is of utmost importance to get your property finance right the first time
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarcia Jansen</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sarcia-jansen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sarcia-jansen/</guid>
      <description> I specialise in assisting clients in obtaining the best financial solutions available. Whether you are buying your first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saxon France</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/saxon-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/saxon-france/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Beattie</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/scott-beattie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/scott-beattie/</guid>
      <description> I am a 26+ year (in 2017) veteran of the insurance and finance industry. Cube Home Loans was established in 2005 and each year that I have been an owner of the business
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Graham</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/scott-graham/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/scott-graham/</guid>
      <description> With more that a decade in financial services we understand that you want fast and efficient service. Let us work together to get your finance sorted efficiently and with a minimum of fuss.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Shanks</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/scott-shanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/scott-shanks/</guid>
      <description> I have been helping people in Adelaide metropolitan are find the best home loan deals for over 25 years. I pride myself on being able to remove the barriers to buying property and making it as easy as possible for my clients. Whether you are buying or selling
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sean Lewis</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sean-lewis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sean-lewis/</guid>
      <description> With more than 20 years experience in the Financial Services Industry as both a Mortgage Broker and Financial Adviser
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sean Martin</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sean-martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sean-martin/</guid>
      <description> A fully accredited mortgage broker in Sydney
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sebastian Lee</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sebastian-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sebastian-lee/</guid>
      <description> A FBAA Accredited Finance Broker conducting as an independent proprietor
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seen Rengasamy</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/seen-rengasamy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/seen-rengasamy/</guid>
      <description> My extensive experience in the Mortgage industry means I can provide that specialised service to my clients. During that period
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sehnaz Gray</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sehnaz-gray/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sehnaz-gray/</guid>
      <description> Located in the Eastern Suburbs of Melbourne I can offer you a vast range of different loan options from major Banks
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selva Chetty</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/selva-chetty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/selva-chetty/</guid>
      <description> Having worked at Finsure Group for over 3 years
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shane Howley</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/shane-howley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/shane-howley/</guid>
      <description> As a Mortgage &amp;amp; Finance Broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shane Khoo</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/shane-khoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/shane-khoo/</guid>
      <description> With so many finance options available in the market today
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shaun Howie</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/shaun-howie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/shaun-howie/</guid>
      <description> Shaun is an experienced professional with over 10 years?? experience as a Director within the Finance industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelley Arora</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/shelley-arora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/shelley-arora/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Bracic</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/simon-bracic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/simon-bracic/</guid>
      <description> I am a mortgage broker that specializes in the residential financial services sector
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Case</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/simon-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/simon-case/</guid>
      <description> With 15 years experience within one of Australia&amp;rsquo;s big 4 lenders
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Gao</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/simon-gao/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/simon-gao/</guid>
      <description> I have been in the industry for 2 years and have successfully helped many different customers settle their properties. I&amp;rsquo;m here to help.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Moore</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/simon-moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/simon-moore/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Poy</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/simon-poy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/simon-poy/</guid>
      <description> I have a passion for making the complicated
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Young</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/simon-young/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/simon-young/</guid>
      <description> Hi
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simone Dalton</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/simone-dalton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/simone-dalton/</guid>
      <description>Simone is passionate about offering excellent customer service and creative financial solutions. Simone has over 13 years of experience in the finance industry including 10 years as a mortgage broker and 3 years working in a bank. There are a lot of products out there and searching the web/online is one way but still requires a lot of time and does not always give accurate information specific to an individual and can result in an application that does not proceed simply because it has not met the client?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simone Tang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/simone-tang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/simone-tang/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sofie Chapman</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sofie-chapman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sofie-chapman/</guid>
      <description> Sofie has a strong background in finance with over 6 years experience in the finance and mortgage lending industry and over 18 years experience as a professional property investor and developer currently holding a portfolio of 10 properties across Australia. Her passion is helping people achieve their financial goals
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sophia Wu</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sophia-wu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sophia-wu/</guid>
      <description> Director and Founder of LESC Financial Services
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephanie Dean</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/stephanie-dean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/stephanie-dean/</guid>
      <description> I am passionate in providing the ultimate customer experience to secure your future and make your financial dreams a reality. The finance market can be tricky to navigate
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Bonfield</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/stephen-bonfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/stephen-bonfield/</guid>
      <description> Stephen Bonfield
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Dinte</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/stephen-dinte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/stephen-dinte/</guid>
      <description> Australian Mortgage Planners offers far more than basic mortgage broking. With over 40 years experience in the finance industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Miller</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/stephen-miller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/stephen-miller/</guid>
      <description> Steve has been in the Finance and Banking services industry for over 35 years enjoying a successful career in Financial Services Sales and Management with Westpac Group. Steve&amp;rsquo;s success in key areas include: SME (Small Medium Enterprise) and Commercial Lending
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Yang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/stephen-yang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/stephen-yang/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Langan</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/steve-langan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/steve-langan/</guid>
      <description> GO Property and Finance is focused on &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;Wealth Creation&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; by providing our clients with excellent financial services and property investment advice to help grow all of our clients property portfolio&amp;rsquo;s. We wish to ensure that a relationship of trust and confidence is established &amp;amp; maintained for all clients and we will act in good faith for the benefit of all of our cleints. &amp;ldquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Morant</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/steve-morant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/steve-morant/</guid>
      <description> My team and I have over 20 years of experience and can tailor a solution to suit your individual needs. Our team will hold your hand through the process and guide you - not only with our expert professional knowledge
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Boyce</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/steven-boyce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/steven-boyce/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Lunn</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/steven-lunn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/steven-lunn/</guid>
      <description> Based in Perth WA I am a member of the Finance365 Team who have won numerous Broking Awards since their establishment in 2013. The most recent being one of the top 25 brokers in 2017. These awards have been achieved due to our unwavering commitment to our clients and providing good old fashioned customer service. At a meeting of your convenience I can evaluate your needs
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Nicholls</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/steven-nicholls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/steven-nicholls/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Vicary</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/steven-vicary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/steven-vicary/</guid>
      <description> Helping people realise their dreams. I have a great job and am passionate about what I do. Whether its helping a young person or couple into their first home
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stevie Von Thees</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/stevie-von-thees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/stevie-von-thees/</guid>
      <description> 18 Years in Consumer Lending. My back ground also includes assessment
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stewart Noble</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/stewart-noble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/stewart-noble/</guid>
      <description> Over 14 years of mortgage broking experience and currently looking after a team of eighteen brokers all over Sydney and Wollongong.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuart Pearce</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/stuart-pearce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/stuart-pearce/</guid>
      <description> I have 11 years experience in Banking
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunil Roy</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sunil-roy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sunil-roy/</guid>
      <description> I have been in Mortgage Broking since 2002 and willing to help clients in any location. I have access to 28 lenders including all majors. I am able to assist First Home buyers
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunny Dhillon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sunny-dhillon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sunny-dhillon/</guid>
      <description> I have extensive knowledge of the finance industry having worked in the Finance sector for over ten years. My approachable personality
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suzanne Luquero</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/suzanne-luquero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/suzanne-luquero/</guid>
      <description> I have been in finance for over 15 years. Starting at the ATO in the UK
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syed Naqvi</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/syed-naqvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/syed-naqvi/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sylvia Kong</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sylvia-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sylvia-kong/</guid>
      <description> I have been in the finance industry for over 12 years. If you are looking for someone who is honest
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tammie Rimon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tammie-rimon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tammie-rimon/</guid>
      <description> I have worked in the banking and finance industry for 12 years now
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tane Taiaroa</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tane-taiaroa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tane-taiaroa/</guid>
      <description> As a mobile mortgage broker I offer my service comparing hundreds of different home loans from over 40 Lenders Including all the majors
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanvir Ahmed</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tanvir-ahmed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tanvir-ahmed/</guid>
      <description> I am an independent broker with no KPIs
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terry Prendergast</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/terry-prendergast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/terry-prendergast/</guid>
      <description> I have been helping clients with their home loan requirements for 8 years. I have wide experience in investment lending as well as Owner Occupied finance. I have my own business and love helping people achieve their financial goals.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thaer Burbar</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/thaer-burbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/thaer-burbar/</guid>
      <description> My name is Thaer Burbar
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theresa Alaimoana</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/theresa-alaimoana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/theresa-alaimoana/</guid>
      <description> I am of Pacific Island descent originally from Auckland
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Chen</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/thomas-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/thomas-chen/</guid>
      <description> Looking for a great Mortgage Broker to Help your home loan application. I am here to help your home loan application easily and less worries. Experienced with 45 different bank s products
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thuy Hook</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/thuy-hook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/thuy-hook/</guid>
      <description> I am prides myself on helping my clients achieve their financial goals and dreams
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tian Xu</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tian-xu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tian-xu/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Bollard</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tim-bollard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tim-bollard/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cavanagh</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tim-cavanagh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tim-cavanagh/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Projeski</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tim-projeski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tim-projeski/</guid>
      <description>  Over 18 years?? experience in Mortgage Broking and Mortgage Management. Bachelor of Commerce (Prop Eco) - I like to focus on showing my Clients how to pay off their home sooner through a detailed mortgage minimisation program. As a result many of them   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Russell</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tim-russell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tim-russell/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the finance industry since 2008 with experience across a range of different firms and dealer groups. During my time in the industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Werner</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tim-werner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tim-werner/</guid>
      <description> I am an independent mortgage broker who always works to put the clients needs first and will work tirelessly on your behalf with a view to building a relationship with my clients that will last a lifetime.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toby Roennfeldt</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/toby-roennfeldt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/toby-roennfeldt/</guid>
      <description> With 10+ years experience in the finance industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Nightingale</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tom-nightingale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tom-nightingale/</guid>
      <description> Tom is a fully accredited mortgage broker and a member of the Mortgage &amp;amp; Finance Association of Australia (MFAA) with over 10 years experience in Financial Services. He holds a Bachelor of Business (Accounting) from the University of Technology
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toni Warren</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/toni-warren/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/toni-warren/</guid>
      <description> Home loan experts with a solid lending foundation of over 16 years working within the financial services industry. We are driven and committed to working with you to realise your dreams of home ownership. With over 30 specialised lenders offering 300 loan solutions
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Chik</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tony-chik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tony-chik/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Ciappara</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tony-ciappara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tony-ciappara/</guid>
      <description> My goal is to provide personalized
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Dion</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tony-dion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tony-dion/</guid>
      <description> I am one of Hobart&amp;rsquo;s most qualified and experienced real estate and mortgage broking licenced advisors who provides a single point of contact service 7 days a week 04**** 846. I am accredited with several banks and non-banks and able to advise on numerous loan products that will suit you now and in the future
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Elkins</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tony-elkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tony-elkins/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Page</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tony-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tony-page/</guid>
      <description> I ve been a business owner for 35 years and owned a number of investment properties before I became a mortgage broker. Believe me I know just how difficult and confusing the home loan process can be. My purpose is to make the process as simple as possible for you while ensuring you end up with a loan that suits your purpose and is right for you.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Rimon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tony-rimon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tony-rimon/</guid>
      <description> Over 30 experience in Banking and Finance. Over 16 years of running my own Finance business
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Xia</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tony-xia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tony-xia/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracey Franco</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tracey-franco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tracey-franco/</guid>
      <description> I am the Owner of FinanceCorp. I have been a mortgage broker for over 11 years and has worked in the Finance Industry for more than 16 years. I am absolutely committed to providing her clients with a service that will exceed their expectations.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracey Pye</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tracey-pye/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tracey-pye/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracy Cox</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/tracy-cox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/tracy-cox/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelly</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/travis-kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/travis-kelly/</guid>
      <description>I can assist you with all your home and personal loan requirements. With the ability to compare home loan options with more than 25 lenders, we can locate the right fit for you and your circumstances. As a Mortgage Choice broker, we get paid the same rate regardless of which home loan you choose from our wide choice of lenders so our home loan advice is at no cost to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trent Fleskens</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/trent-fleskens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/trent-fleskens/</guid>
      <description> Managing Director of Property Development &amp;amp; Finance Specialists
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trent Stokes</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/trent-stokes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/trent-stokes/</guid>
      <description> With over 10 years of finance experience working with both consumers and commercial clientele
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Thomson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/trevor-thomson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/trevor-thomson/</guid>
      <description> Whatever your goals may be
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trina Phillips</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/trina-phillips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/trina-phillips/</guid>
      <description> I have been an independent mortgage broker since 2005 and prior to this
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troy Mcdonald</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/troy-mcdonald/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/troy-mcdonald/</guid>
      <description> I bring more than 20 years?? finance and property experience
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Umit Talarico</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/umit-talarico/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/umit-talarico/</guid>
      <description> I am a mortgage broker and principal at Premier Lending Pty Ltd
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vanessa Lewis</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vanessa-lewis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vanessa-lewis/</guid>
      <description> Your Local Mortgage Broker - Refinancing
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variable Rate Home Loan Comparison</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/compare/variable-rate-home-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/compare/variable-rate-home-loan/</guid>
      <description>Major banks    Ranking Bank Variable Rate Max LVR     1 BankWest 3.72% * 80%   2 UBank 3.74% 80%   3 St George 3.80% 95%   4 Westpac 3.88% * 95%   5 Commonwealth Bank 3.89% * 95%   6 ANZ 4.03% 90%   7 NAB 4.17% 95%    /* Introductory rates

Non-major banks    Ranking Bank Variable Rate Max LVR     1 HSBC 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vase Marcevska</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vase-marcevska/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vase-marcevska/</guid>
      <description> A blemish on your credit file shouldn??t stand in the way of your financial security. At Pepper Money
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaughan Clark</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vaughan-clark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vaughan-clark/</guid>
      <description> A solutions-driven Mortgage and Finance professional providing clients with more choice
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veronica Pavlovich</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/veronica-pavlovich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/veronica-pavlovich/</guid>
      <description> After 30 years in banking industry
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vicki Mundt</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vicki-mundt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vicki-mundt/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victor Shen</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/victor-shen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/victor-shen/</guid>
      <description> With office located in Sydney
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victoria Wakenshaw</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/victoria-wakenshaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/victoria-wakenshaw/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m a mobile Mortgage Broker based in Berowra, servicing the areas of Sydney North Shore, Sydney Northern Beaches up to the Central Coast. I have 26 years of experience and qualifications in the finance industry, both in Corporate Finance and Mortgage Broking. My specialties lie in providing finance solutions for Self Employed applicants, Small Commercial and SMSF loans, however I am more than happy to assist anyone looking for finance, be it an Owner Occupied or Investment loan, First Home Owner, Construction Loan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viktor Desovski</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/viktor-desovski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/viktor-desovski/</guid>
      <description> Viktor commenced his finance career in 2013 when
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vince Scully</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vince-scully/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vince-scully/</guid>
      <description> Lifesherpa is Australia&amp;rsquo;s first online financial advice service tailored to the needs of young Australians. We give you the right advice across home loans, insurance, super budgeting and paying off your debts. AND we give you back the commissions paid by banks and insurance companies - putting money back in your pocket. Ask me how much you can save.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vincent Chipchase</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vincent-chipchase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vincent-chipchase/</guid>
      <description> I have been working in the Finance Industry for over 10 years and in that time I have assisted hundreds of clients with their lending needs. My experience is in all areas of Residential
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vincent Moore</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vincent-moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vincent-moore/</guid>
      <description> I currently work at Entourage Finance
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vincent Yao</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vincent-yao/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vincent-yao/</guid>
      <description> As an accredited mortgage broker
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vishal Behl</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vishal-behl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vishal-behl/</guid>
      <description> An experienced Mortgage Broker and Property Consultant (L.R.E.A) providing expert services to clients looking to invest in both Residential and Commercial property. I assist customers Australia wide with availability extending to after business hours &amp;amp; weekends. My expertise include ?? ?? Home &amp;amp; Investment loans (up to 97% borrowing) ?? Property Investment &amp;amp; Consulting ?? Refinancing ?? Construction Loans ?? Self-Managed Super Funds (SMSF) Loans etc.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walter Bonnet</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/walter-bonnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/walter-bonnet/</guid>
      <description> Having been in the finance industry for over 20 years
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wayne Dickerson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/wayne-dickerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/wayne-dickerson/</guid>
      <description> Experienced, independent non bank aligned broker who is passionate about thinking outside the square for clients looking to purchase for home or investment purposes.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>William Krause</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/william-krause/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/william-krause/</guid>
      <description>Bill enjoys being one of the three loan writers at Navigator Home Loans. He holds Certificate IV Finance and Mortgage Broking and is an Authorised Credit Representative with Team Navigator Pty Ltd. He is a full member of the Mortgage and Finance Association of Australia. He is currently studying to achieve a Diploma of Finance and Mortgage Broking Management. Bill is an experienced property investor but is also passionate about guiding first home buyers and property upgraders by researching and advising the most suitable loans and structures to meet the client?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>