<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ask the Experts on Loans101</title>
    <link>http://loans101.com.au/questions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ask the Experts on Loans101</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Loans101</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://loans101.com.au/questions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>As a self-employed person, I am finding it difficult to find a competitive home loan. What tips can you give to help me find the right lender and also give me the best chance of being approved for a self-employed home loan?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/questions/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/questions/2/</guid>
      <description>Lending to self-employed borrowers can often be complex and requires extensive knowledge of a lender’s requirements. Thankfully some lenders provide more flexible options to suit a self-employed borrower’s differing circumstances.
As a self-employed borrower, you will most likely have to provide more information than the average borrower. This may include BAS statements, tax returns, bank statements or even a declaration from your accountant. If you are able to be quick when providing these items, it will help speed up the application process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How does a lender work out what your borrowing power is? I am looking to take out a home loan, but I’m not sure what information a lender will look at when they are assessing my application.</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/questions/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/questions/6/</guid>
      <description>When a lender calculates your borrowing power, they look at your income and financial commitments and then calculate if you have enough money left over to afford the mortgage repayments. Some factors they look at include: income from your job, share investments, property investments and any family tax income. They look at financial commitments such as credit cards, other loans, other mortgages and HECS debt. They will also look at the total number of applicants and dependants to calculate your average living expenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am ready to start applying for a home loan, but I have no idea where to start when it comes to choosing a lender, what should I be looking for?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/questions/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/questions/1/</guid>
      <description>There are plenty of factors to consider when choosing a lender and it’s important that you do plenty of research. Firstly, take a look at their product range. Not everyone is going to fit the same mold. You may have a different financial or personal situation to other borrowers, which will require a different home loan. Therefore, look for a lender who will offer a range of both specialised and prime home loan products to suit individual needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have heard a lot of differing opinions about refinancing a home loan and I’m not sure who to believe. Is it worth refinancing or will it be too expensive and time consuming?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/questions/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/questions/5/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of myths floating around about refinancing and it is important to decipher fact from fiction before making any decisions. Here are a few myths we’ve busted.
Too costly to refinance: With exit fees being banned on 1 July 2011 (for loans established after this date), refinancing may not cost as much as you would think. Although there may be some fees included to switch lenders, if you find a lender who offers lower interest rates, little or no upfront fees or ongoing fees, you may find that you will receive greater savings over the life of the loan that outweigh these initial fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My partner and I are researching home loans, but we keep seeing the term LMI popping up and we would like to know what it means and how it will affect what home loan we choose?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/questions/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/questions/3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are currently looking for a home loan, but we are not sure what the comparison rate is that is displayed next to the interest rate. Do you we need to worry about that rate?</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/questions/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/questions/4/</guid>
      <description>While it is important to compare interest rates when looking for a home loan, it is just as important, if not more, to compare comparison rates. The idea behind comparison rates was to help borrowers understand how any fees or charges would impact an interest rate to help compare loans from different lenders by revealing the true cost of a loan.. Comparison rates are a handy tool but you need to understand how to use it and its limitations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>