<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Broker Contacts on Loans101</title>
    <link>http://loans101.com.au/directory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Broker Contacts on Loans101</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Loans101</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://loans101.com.au/directory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Lim</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/arthur-lim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/arthur-lim/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;Dual languages English and Indonesian. First home buyer specialist. Investor and debt consolidation specialist.&amp;rdquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Brown</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/christopher-brown/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The team at New Vision Financial Services have access to over 40 different lenders, giving you more flexibility when making a decision. Our consultants have had extensive experience within the banking, financial and corporate sector. At New Vision Financial Services we specialise in finance lending for home, investment, business, commercial, asset, debtor and many other requirements. As New Vision Financial Services has progressed, we have developed strong relationships with professional service providers such as; Financial Planners, Accountants, Settlement Agents, Leasing &amp;amp; Equipment Providers, Debt Management Specialists and many more to allow our clients access to a complete suite of services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iva Rasic</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/iva-rasic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/iva-rasic/</guid>
      <description>As Senior Mortgage Broker for the BorrowRight team, I pride myself in going above and beyond for all our clients. Having worked in Financial Services for over 3 years, I have extensive knowledge of the lending process. In the meantime, I have earned a Commerce Degree (MJR in Marketing) from Macquarie University, completed my Certificate IV in Mortgage Broking and recently completed a Certificate in Real Estate Sales and Property Management from REINSW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Wei</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/jack-wei/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/jack-wei/</guid>
      <description> Our highly experienced team has over 19 years of combined experience in finance industry. During this time, we’ve helped many people significantly improve their financial independence and security. Get to know more about our team and how we can help you.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathy Robinson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/kathy-robinson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/kathy-robinson/</guid>
      <description> As an experienced Mortgage Broker I really enjoy helping people achieve their dreams by securing finance for whatever their needs may be. I lead from the front. I will work with you every step of the way to ensure a smooth and trouble free application process. Calling me will be the best move to make.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicole	Cannon</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/nicolecannon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/nicolecannon/</guid>
      <description> Pink Finance is Australia&amp;rsquo;s most recognised Broker for Ethics, Social Responsibility &amp;amp; Community Engagement. Nicole has been in the industry for 15 years and has a team dedicated to help you achieve your dreams.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oktay Sengoz</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/oktay-sengoz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/oktay-sengoz/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sally Prowse</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sally-prowse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sally-prowse/</guid>
      <description> Sandcastle Finance has been helping people obtain the most appropriate finance for over a decade we are most passionate about showing clients how they can use other peoples money to grow a property portfolio that will ultimately give them a passive income for life
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam Chuang</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/sam-chuang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/sam-chuang/</guid>
      <description>About Sam is an experienced home loan lender with over 10 years working at both local and international banks. Sam is a self taught front end-web developer and UI/UX designer. He responsibled for the operation and the development of Loans101 platform.
If you have any questions or feedback on how to make Loans101 a better place for customers and mortgage brokers, feel free to get in touch with Sam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stewart Noble</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/stewart-noble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/stewart-noble/</guid>
      <description> Over 14 years of mortgage broking experience and currently looking after a team of eighteen brokers all over Sydney and Wollongong.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelly</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/travis-kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/travis-kelly/</guid>
      <description>I can assist you with all your home and personal loan requirements. With the ability to compare home loan options with more than 25 lenders, we can locate the right fit for you and your circumstances. As a Mortgage Choice broker, we get paid the same rate regardless of which home loan you choose from our wide choice of lenders so our home loan advice is at no cost to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victoria Wakenshaw</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/victoria-wakenshaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/victoria-wakenshaw/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m a mobile Mortgage Broker based in Berowra, servicing the areas of Sydney North Shore, Sydney Northern Beaches up to the Central Coast. I have 26 years of experience and qualifications in the finance industry, both in Corporate Finance and Mortgage Broking. My specialties lie in providing finance solutions for Self Employed applicants, Small Commercial and SMSF loans, however I am more than happy to assist anyone looking for finance, be it an Owner Occupied or Investment loan, First Home Owner, Construction Loan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vince Scully</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/vince-scully/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/vince-scully/</guid>
      <description> Lifesherpa is Australia&amp;rsquo;s first online financial advice service tailored to the needs of young Australians. We give you the right advice across home loans, insurance, super budgeting and paying off your debts. AND we give you back the commissions paid by banks and insurance companies - putting money back in your pocket. Ask me how much you can save.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wayne Dickerson</title>
      <link>http://loans101.com.au/wayne-dickerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://loans101.com.au/wayne-dickerson/</guid>
      <description> Experienced, independent non bank aligned broker who is passionate about thinking outside the square for clients looking to purchase for home or investment purposes.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>